请！请！
对不起，我不说话阿！
停止！我不明白！
你现在明白了么？
这是一个杰里科941指着我的头。
你可以得到一个在黑市上为$ 300。
是啊。
这是一个非常可靠的武器。
我的名字是大卫Packouz。
而我是一个国际军火商。
你知道战争是什么？
他们会告诉你这是爱国，民主
或有关其他人的一些狗屎憎恨我们的自由。
但是你要知道它的的确确是？
你看到了什么？
来自阿肯色州的一个孩子做他的爱国义务，以捍卫自己的国家吗？
我看到一个头盔，阻燃手套，
防弹衣，和M16。
我见$ 17,500名。
这就是它的成本来装备一名美国士兵。
超过两百万士兵
在伊拉克和阿富汗作战。
它花费了美国纳税人每年$ 4.5十亿
只需交纳空调票据
对于这些战争。
这就是战争是关于什么的。
战争是一个经济体。
如果谁告诉你，否则
无论是在它的或愚蠢。
但我不知道呢。
那时候，我什么都不知道。
你不能在这里停车。
嗨，老兄。我只是在2150，岸先生得到了一个客户端。
我提前几分钟。
是吗？这是一个大门的社区。
你仍然不能在这里停车。
你可能不应该抽烟，在这里，无论是。
好的。谢谢。
有很多我可以说这个时期在我的生命
这将使上下文这个故事。
我可以告诉你如何
我一个学期后，退了学。
- 怎么就这么左四干什么？ - 它仍然疼痛。
吵了我的父母。
我无论怎样退出或来自六个不同的工作被解雇了。
- 而已。 - 好吧。在那里，我们走了。
但回过头来看，我认为需要理解的最重要的事情是
我完全失去了。
抱歉。它下跌。
这没关系，加里。
我才22岁
按摩丰富的迈阿密海滩花花公子一个小时75块钱。
但我受够了。
是时候改变狗屎。
我有一个大的想法。
我的计划是出售优质床单批发
在南佛罗里达州的所有养老院。
并有数百人。
- 那感觉真是柔软。 - 这应该。
这是埃及棉，400线程数。
我的意思是，这对机构使用的线路中几乎顶部。
我不知道。它似乎过高。
那么，在每单位$ 29日，它远远过量。
大卫，你知道在这里Hilldale居民的平均年龄？
呃，不，我不知道。
- 八十二岁。 - 哇。
你见过在一个82岁的老人皮肤？
你有没有感觉到呢？
是啊。其实，我是一个认证的按摩治疗师
和我的很多客户都是老人。
那么你应该知道。
这些表，
它会像羊绒包装蜥蜴。
你会做吗？
你会在包装的羊绒蜥蜴？
我猜不会。
那么，为什么你会指望我？
我的侄子。
他是很好的，对不对？
我已经沉没我一生的积蓄65案件溢价床单
但我忽略了一个关键因素。
没有人真正关心老人。
你为什么不只是卖他们回来？
它不工作，这样。我买了他们的大头。
我好性交。
你不是性交。
皮特的性交。
他死了。
神圣的狗屎。那是埃夫拉伊姆？
是啊。
我以为他还在洛杉矶。
我也是。
- 他是一位伟大的朋友。 - 谢谢。
他看上去是如此晒黑。
埃夫拉伊姆Diveroli是我最好的朋友，长大了。
但我没有见过他，因为他被运到生活与他在10年级的叔叔。
我想我们的父母希望保持我们相距甚远越好。
有没有在生命册目录。
我们不知道，如果我们正处在一个新的篇章，或故事的结束的开始。
这就是为什么我们每次翻页时间必须感激。
你回来只是为了这个？
他妈的不！我几乎不认识皮特。
我希望在这里见到你。
你知道你妈妈不会给我你的电话号码？
什么，你叫我的房子？
不，我他妈的她。
她还恨我，是吧？
是的，最有可能的。
我很想念你，兄弟。
我也是。
让我们去兜风。
呃...
我不能。我在4:00有一个客户端。
他妈的狗屎。取消它。
你的孩子在城里回来。
来吧！
那么，什么用LA，男人发生了什么？
你为什么回迁？
哦，你知道我是在为我的叔叔，对吗？
是的，我听说你一样，一炮经销商或什么的。
漂亮多了。我的意思是，
我们会在警方拍卖买缴获的武器和转售它们在互联网上。
凉。
这是很酷，直到我叔叔scumbagged我过去70隆重。
神圣的狗屎。七十盛大？
随你。他妈的他。我做了一屁股的债。
我决定，我会回来到迈阿密，开始了我自己的店。
凉。
呦，哪来的这家伙活？
这是一样，五分钟。你有什么地方你得是什么？
没有。
好吧。所以，我想不通这是雪上加霜。
你卖床单到养老院的事实
或者说你这个混蛋家伙了钱。
为了记录在案，我是有执照的按摩师，好吗？
完全合法的。
好的。但最终，球员都来了，对不对？
喜欢，在你的胸部或什么？
你知道吗？去你妈的。
去你妈的，哥们。
兄弟，你还记得我们去买杂草一起是什么时候？
我当然是了。这是他妈的创伤。
是的，但你还记得你的第二天，当我们走进学校
每个人都知道我们被逮捕？
是啊，我们是黑帮，兄弟。
我们认为，我们跑了南海滩。
我们没跑神学院。
我们没有把狗屎任何人。
是的，我错过了。
你错过了神学院？
不，我错过
没有任何人采取狗屎。
哟！
他出来。你在找杂草？
依靠。你有好东西？
这样说吧。我卖了他的狗屎。
什么跟这个黑人，男人了？
凉。你可以做一盎司？
是啊，无汗。三项法案。
三百。我喜欢。
您得到更好的价格，当你来到直接向分销商。
我猜是这样。
好吧。
呀，于是，她打开门。
而我想，“呦。寒意。我是不是那个电视剧。”
你知道我的意思？
“我知道你在摇篮另一个黑鬼”。
这是怎么回事？
什么？
我可以得到狗屎？
什么狗屎？
我只给你$ 300的一些杂草。
任你黑鬼见过这个混蛋过吗？
我是没见过狗屎。
男人，获得他妈的离开这里。
- 好吧。好吧，好吧。 - 是啊。
这个白人男孩疯狂。
降落伞裤。
看起来像杰雷诺和狗屎。
看起来他去教堂。
哟，哟，抱起来，抱起来，人。
- 什么他妈的。 - 妈的！
来吧！哪里是每个人去？
我以为我们会挂出。
什么是一群混蛋的。
什么他妈的是什么？你疯了吗？
这很酷，兄弟。
我有3类枪支许可证。
- 咦？ - 来吧，进去。
我知道附近的其他经销商。
有点奇怪。我们同岁，但我总是抬头埃夫拉伊姆。
当生活踢我，我留了下来。
但不是埃夫拉伊姆。他踢中后卫。
主席先生，我们要感谢你
今天我们参观这里。
我们很荣幸能服务于我们的国家，
和自豪地欢迎你，
我们的战时总司令...
- 嘿。 - 嘿，亲爱的。
怎么样的葬礼？
这是惊人的。
哦，我的上帝。你这样扔石头，不是吗？
咦？什么？
你刚才谈到的葬礼为“惊艳”。
什么？第葬礼是真的很伤心。
是啊，每个人都完全郁闷了。
但是，我遇到了我的朋友从成长。
这家伙我告诉你。埃夫拉伊姆Diveroli？
你被拘捕的人吗？
是啊。我的意思是，我们做了一些其他的东西太多，但...
无论如何，他刚刚搬回到迈阿密。
这是伟大的，对不对？
是啊。我认为他的办公室明天摆动。
我们要抢吃午饭。
- 好的。 - 你饿了吗？
- 嗯？ - 我太饿了。
- 我们没有太多在这里。 - 哦。
- 我的意思是，我们有比萨饼。 - 真的吗？
- 和玉米片。 - 我们有玉米片？
和冰淇淋。
等等，什么？我们从来没有冰淇淋。
你跟我他妈的，不是吗？
之所以如此，是平均值。
这是那么容易。
你好？
您好，先生克斯Borstein。这是大卫Packouz。
你告诉我今天打电话给在11:00。
我有那些床单有我，我很愿意为你去看看。
呃，先生，如果你给我机会
我相信，你的居民
将欣赏的差异。
这是我们无法自圆其说的开支，而我们只是不感兴趣。
嗯。
好了，好了，感谢您的时间。
是啊，这是合同专家
林赛迈克尔斯从陆军司令部，皮卡汀尼。
那就对了。
是啊，我发出了征集一些249s巴士拉
我们似乎已经错位您的文书工作。
大。所以，如果你能继续前进，只是重新给我发电子邮件这些数字。
其实，你知道吗？关于第二个想法，
我们即将就这些提案请求的决定。
你为什么不继续前进，只是给我出价，而我在这里遇到你的电话？
嗯。
而这是否包括弹匣？
大。是的先生。
你不断提供枪支，我们会继续杀死坏人。
上帝祝福你。
什么他妈的一个工具。这是怎么回事，兄弟？
呦，这是怎么回事，人呢？那是什么一回事呢？
哦，那是我冒充军官。
真？做什么的？
要找出我的竞争对手的合同竞标。
这是他妈的天才。
我还以为你说你卖一样，缴获的武器在互联网上枪坚果。
不再。
现在我只卖一个螺母枪。
哦耶？哪一个？
美国军方，狗娘养的。
想要做一个奉击？
漂亮生病了，是吧？
还等什么，你卖这些东西五角大楼？
我出售各种狗屎五角大楼。
枪支，子弹，防弹衣。
上周，我在伊拉克运400防毒面具美国特种部队。
没有狗屎。
你已经多久这样做呢？
两三个月。
你好好赚钱？
哦!他妈的，伙计。
这样说吧。我做了200K，在过去八个星期。
而我只能告诉你，因为你是我的孩子。
我不是吹牛。
神圣的狗屎。
是啊。看一下这个。
美联储商务哎呀代表联邦商业机会。
认为易趣，而是战争。
- 他们购买这里的坦克？ - 兄弟，他们买这里的一切。
这是疯了。
政府有一个公共网站
含每一项军事合约目前最高出价。
但我跳过大件商品，寻找小球狗屎
巨国防承包商忽视。
每个人的战斗在同一个馅饼。
但他们忽略了面包屑。
我住在面包屑，像老鼠。
而当你在处理与五角大楼，面包屑价值数百万。
这些列表似乎永远继续下去。
而根据埃夫拉伊姆，他们做到了。
谢啦。
所以，我不明白这一点。
如果有一个完整的国防工业，
为什么五角大楼想要买你的东西？
他们不希望，他们不得不这样做。
还记得小联盟？
怎么样，在本赛季结束后，他们会发出那么大MVP奖杯
而一个孩子会总是赢吗？
是啊，埃文塔尔博特。
对。但后来，一年下来，别人的妈妈抱怨？
然后，他们不得不给大家一个小奖杯，这样他们就不会心疼？
即使是脂肪智障的孩子，罗比・弗里德曼，得到了一个。
这有点像这里发生了什么。
我仍然困惑的男人。
五角大楼搞砸了，当他们重建伊拉克军队。
他们给这些没有竞标的合同，切尼的男生，他们被抓住了。
因此，布什开始了这一举措公平的竞争环境
现在每购买五角大楼，每枪，手榴弹每次，
每颗子弹，被提供给小企业的投标。
而且肯定的是，大狗仍然获得大奖杯。
但五角大楼的得给小奖杯
对世界上所有的罗比弗里德曼。
所以，基本上，你是一个胖孩子迟缓。
兄弟，我是最胖最迟钝。
在今天的演讲中，布什总统说，相反的报告
他没有攻打伊朗的计划。
总统说，“这是荒谬的。
“我们甚至还没有计划时，我们打伊拉克。”
大卫。
是吗？
还记得几个星期前，在汽车上的家离我妈妈的房子的方式吗？
是。是的，我愿意。
好了，这件事发生。
如何他妈的你打算喂养婴儿？
你有没有想过这一点？
你会怎样做？
混蛋男人把你的余生？
是的，就是这个计划。我会被急拉断男人养活我的孩子。
抱歉。
好的。嗯，至少你认为它通过。
这不好笑。
老兄，我这么性交。
我想你应该为我来的工作。
你在说什么？
说真的，我所需要的帮助。
大卫看着我。
布什在伊拉克打开了闸门。
这是一个他妈的淘金热。
这是非常好的你，埃夫拉伊姆。
他妈的太好了！谁在乎好看？
我一直在寻找把别人上一段时间了。
问题是，我不相信任何人。
但你是我的孩子。
我的意思是，没有犯罪，但我反对这场战争。
我和IZ打算集会和请愿签名。
是啊，老兄，我是反对战争了。
我他妈的恨布什。
但是，这不是关于是支持战争。
战争正在发生。
这是一个关于是亲钱。
更埃夫拉伊姆聊过，它越有意义。
此外，相比于我的其他前景，
这是一个千载难逢的机会。
我唯一的问题是，我会告诉IZ？
我认为这是一个好主意。
所以，我撒谎了。
你知道，我一直在这个行业相信。
我告诉她，有埃夫拉伊姆在政府巨大的联系。
而不是卖床单
以吝啬养老院
我们现在会卖片到自由消费，
资金过剩美军。
这是天才。
我只好撒谎。 IZ痛恨战争。
她有两个表兄弟在伊拉克服役。
她还恨那个被占用了一半的公寓床单的山。
我在处理武器速成班在接下来的六个星期。
在赫斯塔尔556轻机枪。
比利时，但在很多地方下发许可证。
当它来到这个狗屎，埃夫拉伊姆什么都知道了。
制造，型号，重量，它被制成。
请记住，还有的是天安门事件以来对中国的武器禁运。
而如果有要播放的角度，他知道这一点。
你有这个东西的字里行间。
所有的钱都被字里行间的。
我会花我整天淘政府网站，
搜索忽视的合同，我们可以挤压我们的方式进入。
嘿，我觉得我得到的东西。
嘿，格鲁吉亚，我得给你回电话。
然后，在半夜
我们会回到办公室，工作电话。
锻造的关系
与武器制造商遍布东欧。
不，大卫Packouz来自AEY。
我告诉IZ我们正在做在巴基斯坦板材供应商的电话会议。
他们呼吁的家伙像我们这样的战争犬。
底部馈线谁赚钱战
没有在战场上永远踩着脚下。
它是贬义的，但我们还挺喜欢它。
你他妈的人渣一块狗屎！
淹没，混蛋，淹死！
非常好。
拉尔夫斯拉斯基是埃夫拉伊姆的沉默伙伴。
他是一名当地商人
谁拥有14干洗店全部横跨迈阿密。
为什么没人告诉我先生被打破？
拉尔夫出钱来支持这些交易，以换取该公司的25％。
或者至少是他以为是25％。
我们在做上帝的工作，拉尔夫。
我们真的是。
要知道，每一个犹太人欠的债到以色列。
在我看来，这不是一个隐喻的债务。
拉尔夫的印象是埃夫拉伊姆是一个细心的犹太人
谁只涉及武器的一种手段
以保护以色列不受她的敌人。
精美的说。
你碰巧赶上上周五的Torah部分？
- 我最喜欢的之一。 - 同样在这里。
这让我想起这个故事我曾经读过的。
关于一个年轻男子前往平斯克。
这是埃夫拉伊姆的天才。
他会找出谁有人希望他成为
他会成为那种人。
啊!
和他有一样，他们中的20,000。
大。你在哪里找到这个家伙？
你还记得维克多乌克兰？
是的，一个具有Mk3s？
是啊。他使我对这个公司在塞浦路斯。
它是由这家伙，亨利・吉拉德运行。
亨利吉拉德？
是啊，你认识他吗？
你说亨利吉拉德？
一些时间。为什么？他是谁？
好家伙，过去20年来，这家伙已经基本供应
地球上的每个冲突双方。
他是一个他妈的动物。
真？他为什么给我打电话？
因为他是一个他妈的动物。
这是所有的钱，它的所有事项。
嘿，真身，你要去哪里？
我试图找到我的朋友。
你要赚一些钱？
对不起？
我给你$ 1,000现在
如果我们快进到我们的第三次约会。
这是什么意思，甚至？
这意味着我们只是有一个伟大的晚餐，也许满足你的朋友的一些饮料
现在你要打击我在我的车。
我们能不能得到正确的那部分？
谁他妈的是你吗？
埃夫拉伊姆Diveroli。
这是我最好的朋友，大卫。
而且我们的国际军火商。
不过你已经知道，
因为我们对我们的第三次约会。
- 这是怎么回事？ - 没什么，兄弟。
我即将离开这里与我的女孩。
什么他妈的，男人！
哦，我的上帝。
那家伙不是他妈的左右。
是啊，你应该选择了一个不同的女孩。
他妈的说，它几乎工作。
嘿，你还记得你上六年级的战斗埃里克Moscowitz？
是啊，他这样做风车的事情与他的怀里。
这是症状越严重。他是不可战胜的。
你还记得那些歌？
而已。
好家伙，他会杀了我，如果你没有在跳。
大概。嗯。
嘿，我从来不说“谢谢”。
对于一切。
来吧，你知道你有多少帮了我最近。
这个很酷。你不必做很奇怪，没事吧？
嘿，我们可以订购一些食物？
真身，来吧。我本来可以去古巴和背部。
满足家庭，抓住了几个三明治。
我现在已经完成。
你好？
是的先生。对不起，我没想到工作呼叫这么晚。
对，当然。这是上午9:00巴格达。
是谁？
这是个好消息，队长桑托斯。
是的先生。
我们将马上上。
谢谢。再见。
什么？
我们刚刚得到了贝雷塔的交易。
获得他妈的离开这里。
我向上帝发誓。
贝雷塔交易是巨大的。
这是比任何事情到目前为止，我们会关闭大10倍。
这是一个新的水平狗屎。
这就是我他妈的说什么！
这是真正的钱，混蛋！他妈的！
你知道，我们要作出600K
在这他妈的事情吗？
神圣的狗屎。
大卫，你的30％，为$ 180,000元。
圣臭狗屎！
这是惊人的。
我一直用工作埃夫拉伊姆两个月
并且已经大约赚更多的钱
比按摩的一生。
听。
那是什么？
这就是你的宝宝的心跳。
哇。
你能相信它的速度有多快？
- 这是否正常？ - 完全正常。
胎儿有更快的速度心脏比我们做的。
看。
所以，你们想知道的性别？
我们不断来回就可以了。
- 你有什么感想？ - 嗯...
这是工作。我不得不把它。
我很抱歉。
这是大卫。
这是桑托斯上尉在巴格达
检查我的Berettas的交货状态。
队长，好从你的来信。
是的，我们目标。都好。
大。我很担心
这些枪来直接出意大利。
绝对。他们是的，先生。
Packouz，请告诉我
你知道意大利上周通过的立法。
一个禁止所有武器运到伊拉克。
我根本不知道他在说什么。
但是，这是一个巨大的他妈的问题。
Berettas是一个意大利的枪。
制成，并在意大利制造。
呃...
当然。
我是。我一直在手机上
过去三天，做其他安排。
大。这就是我想听到的。
伊拉克警察部队取决于你。
嗯，你告诉他们AEY已经得到了他们所覆盖。
- 突出。 - 谢谢你，队长。一会再聊。
一切都好？
是啊。是的，一切都很好。
发生了什么？我们已经做了什么？
是啊。你猜怎么了？
这是一个女孩。
宝宝。
好的。至少我碰到了什么东西。
说真的，什么他妈的我们该怎么办？
放松，兄弟。
我是不是应该给他回电话，告诉他真相？
什么时候说的是实话曾经帮助别人吗？
埃夫拉伊姆，我们不能家伙这个家伙周围
然后不给。
我们要交付。我已经想通了。
我们用乔丹。
乔丹戈德法布？
约旦...
约旦国家。
这股与伊拉克的边界。这是美国的盟友。
而最重要的，没有禁运。
好了，我们怎么告诉意大利人？
他妈的他们！至于他们而言
他们在5000发送到Berettas他们有没有问题的国家。
我们所要做的就是船炮
从约旦到巴格达。
这就是所谓的规避。
这是否合法？
这不是非法的。
想试试吗？
该慈善机构的事情怎么走？
这是5K，对不对？
它应该是一个5K。
呃，我完成了约1的K吧。
所以，我也许应该退回的钱五分之四。
所以，安德鲁告诉我
你和埃夫拉伊姆现在一起工作？
真？
是啊，我告诉她关于纸张的事情。
是啊。埃夫拉伊姆与政府的一些接触。
所以，我们只是现在强强联合。
是啊，只是......只是要小心他。
- 艾米丽，不要。 - 什么？
你是什??么意思？
那么，他的表妹，丽贝卡，是我的一个老朋友。
我们去露营在一起。
她告诉我，他从她的父亲偷了$ 7万人。
哇，真的吗？
那很有意思。
其实，我听说这是周围的其他方式。
他的叔叔是谁从他那里偷了钱的人。
看到？你不知道。
每个人都有自己的故事版本。
不，我敢肯定。
他们全家停止了它跟他说话。
哟！你为什么不回答你的电话吗？
嘿，这是怎么回事，人呢？
他妈的是什么？
每个人，这是大卫的贸易伙伴，埃夫拉伊姆。
- 嗨，老兄。 - 嗨，老兄。
兄弟，我能和你聊外面一分钟？
- 这很紧急。 - 嗯，当然咯。
并记录在案，我也是他最好的朋友，
所以也许应该被邀请到任何这是。
你看，这些都是她的朋友。这是她的晚宴。
罗森是她的朋友呢？这他妈的犹太人？
相信我，你不想在这里。
我不希望到这里来，行吗？
现在，这是怎么回事？
约旦海关查获我们Berettas。
- 什么？为什么？ - 我不知道他妈的，大卫。
我从高中辍学，他们涵盖国际外交了。
- 那是谁？ - 操，这是桑托斯。
他知道！
把它捡起来，我要听。
- 选择......拿起手机他妈的。 - 这是大卫。
是啊，我刚才听到我的枪是在约旦举行的。
桑托斯队队长，是的，有过轻微的打嗝。
它们是什么做的，即使在约旦？
不用担心。
他们在安曼一个机库。完全安全的。
我和我的团队现在正在研究解决方案。
你没有回答我的问题。
什么他妈的是我的枪在约旦做什么？
桑托斯队队长，这是埃夫拉伊姆Diveroli。
AEY公司总裁，先生。
大卫已告知我的情况，我们正在寻找的选择，因为我们说话。
选择？什么样的选择？
那么，你熟悉的大嘴TP1 9？
这是巴西，它是狗屎。
合同说Berettas，我想Berettas。
主席先生，我需要你与我们合作一点点这个。
让我说清楚。
我在世界的屁股裂缝，捍卫你的自由。
和我同你狗屎袋工作？
你看，我不知道
如果这些Berettas真的在安曼或者如果你只是想鹅您的利润
就像你惨了，老鼠他妈的界每隔一块狗屎。
无论哪种方式，你在危及我的使命。
我关闭你失望。
我取消你的事业。
入门取消原因是判了死刑。
这意味着我们永远不会赢得另一份合同。
上尉，请不要这么做。
我知道你很烦恼。
但是，从一个基督徒另一
我的妻子和我有严重的财政问题。
我们的儿子，卢卡斯，是在医院里。
医疗费用是通过屋顶。
如果你这样做，它会毁了我。它会毁了我的家庭。
正如上帝为我作证，
我将让你你的枪。
你好？
什么他妈的一块狗屎！你相信这他妈的家伙？
- 他妈的。 - 这是怎么回事？
什么枪，大卫？
你他妈的在开玩笑吗？
你告诉我你们在卖床单。
是啊，我还告诉你，我们也卖其他的东西。
我以为你说的枕头！
你看，我不能给予按摩支持孩子。
好的？没有人在买床单。
不，大卫，你骗我。
因为我知道你是怎么想的战争。
我想我们都觉得这种方式！
我怀孕五个月了！
而且它的，如果我不能信任的人有问题
我有一个孩子了！
- 当然，你可以信任我。 - 真的吗？
因为五分钟前，我甚至不知道你是军火商！
我不是一个军火商。
我们做的是完全合法的。
我们为政府工作。我们是中间商。
我们不碰枪，我们没有看到炮声。
我们甚至从来没有离开办公室。
嘿，不好意思打断。这是时间敏感的。
大卫，你有护照？
什么？是的为什么？
我们必须去约旦。就像，尽快。
拉直这狗屎了。
我们得说话，不管，好吗？
是啊。
哟，你的窗口或过道？
- 对不起，对不起。 - 是的，我们刚刚降落。
- 对不起。 - 使馆打电话？
对不起。好的再见。
- 对不起，那种紧急情况。 - 对不起。抱歉。
别担心，我得先走了。我是美国人。
对不起。
美国大使馆提供很少或几乎没有帮助
在处理与海关部。
因此，我们采取了事态到我们自己的手中。
他说，您的许可证已过期
而且你不能飞你的箱子从约旦河而不之一。
是的，我们知道。这就是为什么我们在这里。
你看，我们被告知，你认识的人在政府，
这也许可以帮助我们。
他说，这将需要六周的时间来获得新的许可证。
是啊，这是个问题。我们没有六个星期。
我们今天需要我们的枪。
你看，我不想摘下来的丑陋的美国人在这里。
也许我不明白你的文化的仪式
但这种感觉就像一瞬间
我们都应该向他提供一份礼物，我是正确的？
- 你是对的。 - 好吧。
$ 1,400所美国很酷？
帅气的男人。
本来刚开始，你知道，保存所有这些废话。
我喜欢你的阴影。
告诉他我给他100块钱的色调。
告诉他在胡言乱语。
没门。鳄鱼。
对，我知道。一世...
这是鳄鱼。它实际上是一只鳄鱼。
我喜欢花哨的狗屎，那是我的事。
告诉他。
整整三天，我们什么也没听见。
这是荒谬的。
我们的整个业务是骑在一个11岁的翻译的话。
混蛋！他撕开我们送行！
我们不知道呢。
没有！我知道是什么感觉喜欢他妈的某人。
我也知道这是什么感觉的话，被人性交。
而我们刚刚性交。
你需要冷静下来。
我怎么冷静下来，大卫？
我们正处在一个穆斯林国家，我甚至无法获得口交！
太丢脸了！
这是乱来了！他妈的！
是啊。
马上？
我们下来。
这是阿拉丁。他们在大厅。
看到了吗？来吧。
坚持，稍等。你他妈的在开玩笑吗？
有什么问题？
你想你的枪后，他拿到了你的枪回来。
什么？不，我们说我们需要一个允许他们飞到伊拉克。
没错，但你并不需要许可证来驱动它们。
你希望我们给他们开车到伊拉克？
为什么不？万宝路是所有乔丹的最佳走私犯。
谁，这一点？
这是所有乔丹的最佳走私？
是啊，他开车到巴格达三，每月四次。
埃夫拉伊姆，你想在这里有多重？
呦，它有多远巴格达？
- 为什么你要问他了吗？ -  800公里。
他知道自己在做什么？
埃夫拉伊姆，停止。
-  100％最好。 - 来吧。
这就像500英里。我们将从早上在那里。
你认真想开车到巴格达？
大卫，我们gunrunners。
让我们去运行一些他妈的枪。
我们走吧。
来吧。
嘿，说真的，这是安全的？驾车前往巴格达？
是的，很安全。
50-50。
50-50？我们死了什么，像50％我们的生活，50％？
是。这就是为什么我们通过夜间驾驶。
它是更安全。
如何更安全？
50-50。
兄弟，什么他妈的！
很显然，他不知道是什么意思50-50。
哦，我的上帝。
嘿，关于气什么关系吗？这是一个漫长的旅程，不是吗？
没问题。汽油在伊拉克的自由。
别开玩笑了。
- 游离气？ - 是啊。
看到我在说什么？伊拉克涂料。
我想买一台地方出现。
游离气体。
他妈的凉爽，人。
那是什么？
什么？
你不明白吗？
什么他妈的？
嘿，你为什么放缓，男人呢？
没事的，没事的。
什么是好？
哇，哇。什么他妈的，兄弟？
没关系。边境。
这是什么？
他妈的。
- 耶稣。 - 放下。
- 咦？ - 放下。
哇，哇。
香烟。
为你。
欢迎。
它是超现实他妈的。
半年前，我在迈阿密海滩按摩治疗师。
而现在，在这里我是，驾驶枪的卡车
通过伊拉克沙漠
从初中我最好的朋友。
万宝路？
嘿，万宝路？
兄弟！
有一个在加油站一具尸体！
什么他妈的！
我们在哪？哪里是万宝路？
你没听见我刚才说的？
有一个他妈的尸体在那里，男人！
是的，我听说你。
好吧，我们在一个战区，兄弟。
有尸体，放松。
好吧，我要撒尿。
什么？
小心。
我很好，兄弟。我知道如何采取小便，好吗？
拉屎。
他妈的。
- 你好？ - 嘿。
嘿，宝贝，一切都好吗？
是啊。
那里现在是几点呢？
这是，嗯，在早晨7:30。
妈的，我把你吵醒？
不，我只是在酒店。我们要吃点早餐。
听着，我不是说我喜欢它，
但我得到你为什么这样做。
你做？
这整个过程中我从来没有想过你必须经历的。
所有你下的压力。
它只是杀死我的大话。
这让我觉得我在这孤独。
不，你不是仅此。
我要你知道，你能告诉我什么，大卫。
我们的合作伙伴，还记得吗？
大卫？
是啊，我得叫你马上回来。
- 一切都好吗？ - 是啊，一切都很好。
我正要给你打电话回来，好吗？
我爱你。再见。
埃夫拉伊姆！
- 什么？ - 看！
万宝路！
他妈的！什么他妈的，兄弟。
神圣的狗屎，他们有枪，男人！
我知道！
走吧，走吧！来吧。
什么他妈的！这将无法启动！
凡他妈的是万宝路？
- 我知道了！ - 走！走！
不不不！
等待，等待，等待！
等待！没有！
跑，狗娘养的！跳！
天啊！他们越来越近。来吧，伙计。走！
走吧，走吧！
来吧！
你在跟我开玩笑吗？
我们在费卢杰停气？
你他妈的便宜！
走！
去你妈的，万宝路！
他妈的。
他妈的。他妈的。
我们是怎么死的！
你想开车到巴格达，你这个混蛋！
他们停止。
什么他妈的？看。
圣他妈的，兄弟。
哦，他妈的！好吧！
上帝保佑切尼的美国！
看看这他妈的地方。哦，我的上帝。
对不起，先生？
什么？
这里有一些人要见你。
一些球员？
什么样的人呢？
嘿，万宝路！
给我们一个微笑，华丽。
让我看那些珍珠黄色。
你就像一个伊拉克汤姆・谢立克，兄弟。
你们是AEY？
是的先生。大卫Packouz。
这是我的同事，埃夫拉伊姆Diveroli。
我们采访的电话。
我记得。
你开这些？
过死三角？
他妈的一个正确的我们做到了。
基普，带这些孩子到笼子里，让他们支付。
向右走，先生。
我错了你们两个。
大他妈的工作，男孩。
大他妈的工作。
神圣的狗屎，死亡三角，兄弟？
那就对了。这就是AEY保证，婊子。
我们通过所有三角形驱动，包括你妈妈的。
嘿，硖，我们捕捉的照片，伙计。
好吧。
准备？
- 如何是我的头发？ - 这是很好的，穿好了。
谢谢。
- 得了你。 - 让我看看。
赫尔穆特・牛顿他妈的在这里。
好吧，伙计。
- 完美。 - 好吧，好吧。
让我们去得到他妈的支付。
神圣的狗屎。
疯了吧？ $ 12.2十亿。
这一切都从自己的教父查获。
你们叫萨达姆的教父？
看看所有这些现金，兄弟。你会打电话给他？
$ 280万美元。
- 这里签字。 - 你说对了。
我们得到了一个军队护送到机场
并得到了他妈的巴格达。
有现金近$ 3万
塞进我军颁发的行李袋。
你可能会认为后挣扎在生死线伊拉克
那我们就来完成。
但是你错了。
你看，贝雷塔交易把我们在地图上。
在那之后，我们就开始杀死它。
我们买保时捷匹配。
我们在同一栋大楼买了两套公寓。
哦，我的上帝。
神圣的狗屎，兄弟。
哦!
喔！
拉尔夫很高兴与他的回报
他增加了他的原始投资
在AEY 1000万$。
这给了我们足够的资本去追求更多的交易
扩大公司。
这正是我们所做的。
我不能强调这一点。
你必须要精练这个网站。
日夜。
它是由分钟更新。
有募捐数万本网站上。
每个人是40至50页。
如果你看到一些有趣的事情，
你把它给我。
如果你把它给我，
我会让你发财。
事实上，18个月前，
大卫在这里是抽风了钱的家伙。
实际上，这不是事实。
这绝对是一个事实。
现在，他驾驶一辆保时捷。
那是因为AEY所有。
你有什么问题吗？
嗯，我有一个问题。
什么是AEY立场？
你什么意思？像道德？
不，我的意思是什么字母是什么意思？
这是他妈的...
什么是IBM代表什么？没有。
它只是...只是听起来专业。
呃，其实，IBM代表了国际商业机器公司。
你说什么？
IBM代表国际商业机器。
获得他妈的离开这里。
我是认真的。你不会在这里工作。
获得他妈的我的办公室，你他妈的书呆子！
走！
并记录在案，AEY并不代表什么。
他妈的！什么家伙。
有没有人有任何问题吗？
睡觉。我得到了她。
好吧。好吧。
你好。
我知道。
我知道。没关系。
好的。
什么？
360000 SVD狙击步枪。
1,084,000 GP-30榴弹。
45000 SKO航空火箭弹。
五角大楼的武装阿富汗人在未来30年。
他们正在建造一个全军。
等一下，这一定是一个错字。
不是。
亿发AK-47弹药？
兄弟，这些都不是面包屑。
这是整个他妈的馅饼。
在国防承包商，
这将来到被称为阿富汗的交易。
这将是最大的机会
AEY将永远看到的。
我们不得不去了。
所以，你在哪里去武装整个国家？
拉斯维加斯X是在那里的军事和制造商
一起来揭开战争中的最新产品。
这就像动漫展手榴弹。
当然，大多数人并不知道谁是AEY。
但是，我们看到，作为一个优势。
- 你有你的名单？ - 得到它了。
- 你感觉良好？ - 是啊，我感觉还不错。
要知道，这是不是在手机上开展业务的不同。
当他们看到我们，他们会看到两个孩子。
因此，我们必须向他们展示我们的球。
得到它了。
我们需要他妈的打手，你明白吗？
了解。
好吧，好了。让我们杀了这个狗屎。
但它是一个完整的灾难。
我们很快了解到，
即使我们可以降落阿富汗交易，
这将是一个后勤恶梦。
杰里，很高兴见到你。
到源这种规模的交易
将意味着拼凑
来自世界各地的多个供应商。
哇，哇。
离开这里。
这将需要几十航运的服装
和数以百计的许可证。
我们需要亿发子弹。
所有这一切可能是没关系的主要国防承包商。
但不适合我们。
说实话，我们是我们的联赛。
更改$ 10,000。
今天运气好的话？
埃夫拉伊姆！
这是怎么回事，兄弟？
你去了哪里啊？你为什么不回答你的电话吗？
我与一个妓女。这是怎么回事？
好吧，你要穿好衣服，现在跟我来。
好吧，嗯，给我
38分钟。
埃夫拉伊姆，亨利・吉拉德下来吧，等待着我们。
获得他妈的离开这里。
我死了认真的。
拉屎。
好的。
亨利・吉拉德是军火商之间的传奇。
当他们挂萨达姆反人类罪
有人说，亨利卖给他们的绳子。
嗨，亨利，对不起，我来晚了。
这是我的搭档，我告诉你有关。
- 埃夫拉伊姆Diveroli。 - 很高兴见到你。
这是一个绝对的快乐。
亨利在10分钟吃饭，
但我想你第一手听到这个。
我给他看了名单，他可以提供帮助。
大。随着哪一部分？
所有的。
他可以填补整个订单。
- 整个订单？ - 嗯，嗯。
即使是AK弹药？
不是一个问题。
你知道它的100万发，对不对？
亨利在阿尔巴尼亚的接触。
阿尔巴尼亚？
他们花了几十年对于没有来西方的入侵做准备。
那国家是一个巨大的军火库。
这一切都只是坐在那里。
告诉他最好的部分。
他们在加入北约的过程中，
所以他们必须处理他们所有的苏联时代的武器。
他们是从字面上拆解它，并把它变成废品。
我可以得到最狗屎的对美元的便士。
现在，告诉他其他的最好的部分。
您现在看到的整个他妈的事情的独家代理。
这是灵丹妙药。
一个供应商谁能够填满整个阿富汗的交易。
这不仅让我们在争。
我们可能真正赢得这个事情。
对不起，我有一个问题。
当然。
有了这样转播
你为什么不只是竞标合同上自己？
全面披露？
我是从做任何生意与美国政府禁止。
我是一个观察名单。
像恐怖分子观察名单？
嗯，嗯。
- 得到它了。 - 等等，什么？
好吧，多少的AK弹药？
-  10仙圆。 - 这是他妈的惊人。
而关于航运什么？
您可以通过俄罗斯飞行员得到伊留申76。
每次飞行80K。
对不起，你是一个恐怖分子监视名单上吗？
什么他妈的！
你的国土安全工作？放松，兄弟。
你们两个也许应该讨论这个问题。
我们将会。但是我们非常有兴趣。
好。我的航班明天早上10点离开。
我不能在这个破花费超过48小时。
这就是我经常说。拉斯维加斯是一个为期两天的小镇。
我说的是美国。
我们谈论到储备独占访问
的苏联集团的非制式武器和弹药。
这就是要赢得这场交易对我们来说。
他是一个恐怖分子观察名单上！
随你。人最终名单上的剪刀把上飞机！
这不是为什么他就行了。
你看，五角大楼希望亿发AK-47弹药
在全球范围内不足的中间。
在哪里你觉得他们认为这将从何而来？
一堆黑幕怎么就那样的家伙。
这是作业。
要与地方的人做生意
美国政府不能直接做生意。
就这么简单。
他妈的！
嘿，小伙子们。
所以我们讨论它，我们想继续前进。
太棒了。恭喜。
- 但我们必须要看到的商品。 - 哦，当然。
在现场，在人。
你们去过阿尔巴尼亚？
老实说，直到昨晚
我甚至不知道这是一个真正他妈的国家。
哦，这是一个美丽的地方。
来吧，我会打电话给我的人，我们将对其进行设置。
阿尔巴尼亚是很多东西。
但是，一个美丽的地方是不是其中之一。
我们花了三个独立的航班
和22小时才能到达那里。
亨利的人发来驱动
来接我们到机场
的家伙不会停止说话。
我摔倒了，她恢复了我。
但这些都不是减少埃夫拉伊姆的热情。
他真的相信这可能是答案。
欢迎您，AEY。
我是伊利Pinari，
阿尔巴尼亚最大的军事出口公司的负责人。
埃夫拉伊姆Diveroli。很高兴见到你。
这是我的同事，大卫Packouz。
- 很高兴见到你。 - 你好吗？
呃...
谢谢你的迹象。
哦。这是给你的。
是的我知道。我说谢谢你的迹象。
那么，告诉我们你得到了什么。
这是什么地方？
存储阿尔巴尼亚军队。
我们有700多个像它遍布全国各地。
你有700仓库这样吗？
不只是仓库。
我们使用的教堂，医院，学校。
阿尔巴尼亚是多数武装的国家在世界上。
嘿，这很酷。恭喜，兄弟。
这就像在一个有他妈的博物馆。
大多数这种狗屎没见过日光
自冷战。
但是，这并没有关系给我们。
我们所关心的是AK弹药。
没关系。我们有很多的你来干什么。
所有这些容器都充满了你的子弹。
你是什??么意思，所有的子弹就在这里？
1.26亿发子弹。
他妈的我。
是啊。他妈的我们所有人。
这些几岁了？
30，也许40年。 AK-47的子弹
可以永远持续下去，如果妥善保存。
对。那么，如何进行这些存储？
呃，谁给一个他妈的如何将这些被储存？
所有重要的是，他们的工作他妈的。
他们工作吗？
你试试。
他们他妈的奏效。
整个国防工业争先恐后了这笔交易。
而钥匙就坐在23海运集装箱
在生锈了仓库在世界的另一边的后面。
我们回来只用足够的时间
提交政府的最后期限之前我们的申办。
然后我们等待着。
我们等了五个月。
霸。
大卫！
- 那是埃夫拉伊姆？ - 什么？
- 是吗？ - 大卫！
他妈的，我们赢了！
神圣的狗屎。我们赢得了阿富汗的交易。
- 什么？ - 我们赢得了阿富汗交易！
- 我们赢了？ - 我们他妈的赢了！
兄弟！你他妈的在开玩笑吗？
- 我们他妈的赢了！ - 是啊，混蛋！
是啊！是啊，混蛋！
在我们可以开始，
AEY仍然需要由政府来审核。
这是一个痛苦在屁股过程
涉及到三个独立的审计
和一个人的采访。
审计工作是最大的障碍。
我的意思是，我们甚至没有一个真正的簿记员。
我们没有真正的书籍。
我们不得不编造AEY会计
回去三年。
总帐，银行对账单，假采购订单，
我们结下了一切。
两个星期后，我们在岩石岛，
伊利诺斯州为我们的大型会议
从美国军方采购人员。
我们是相当他妈的紧张。
所以埃夫拉伊姆认为这会是一个好主意，让在停车场高。
耽误。
这听上去像我们两个以上的人的权利吗？
是啊。
这是真正的强者狗屎。
好的。
这是非常令人印象深刻。
非常令人印象深刻。
坦率地说，我们担心你的表现的历史一点点
针对这种规模的交易。
但应符合你们两个照面后，
我们觉得我们在这一个良好的手中。
好了，我们不会让你失望，
先生们。
更何况，
您的出价是太有吸引力让我们欲罢不能。
谢谢。我的意思是，这是伟大的，听到的，因为我们真的很努力这一点。
抱歉。对不起。
一个你刚才说的
我们的报价是太有吸引力错过。
那你的意思，是什么呢？
他对你的男孩lowballed的狗屎了你的竞争对手。
是啊。呃...
多少？
百万。
好的。
只是我。一世...
我很好奇，有多少百万？
那么，在技术上，我们不应该讨论与您，
但什么是地狱。
你们来到比最接近的竞争对手低53个$万元。
他妈的！他妈的！
混蛋！
$ 53个亿美元。
我们准备好了。
看看好的一面。
这一次，美国纳税人
越来越国防合同一个很好的协议。
男人，他妈的美国纳税人。
你好？
IZ？
嘿，艾拉。你好。
亲爱的，你怎么样？
嘿。你知道她的蓝色凉鞋？
哦，嘿嘿。
嗯，我不知道。
但听着，我们可以谈一秒钟？
嗯，嗯。
我需要回去阿尔巴尼亚几个星期。
一个月，上衣。
当然。没问题。
嘿，怎么了？
艾拉和我打算留下来跟我妈一会。
什么？你在说什么？
IZ，发生了什么？
你怎么没告诉我你去伊拉克？
我一直在寻找的水管工的数量
您的计算机上，我看到的照片。
我可以解释。
你说你从来没有离开约旦的酒店房间。
我知道。因为我不想吓坏你。
为什么每次都是它，我抓住你的谎言
你试图说服我，你骗我的好处？
在什么时候，你只是承认你是个骗子？
IZ，你会停下来，好吗？
我们说我们会告诉对方一切。
- 你保证过！ - 我知道！好吧，我搞砸了。
还有什么你不告诉我？
- 没有。 - 号
认真。
你现在知道的一切。
好的。你不是要问我为什么叫水管工？
好，当然。发生了什么？
管道漏水的客用浴室。
我找到了这个。
让我猜猜。你不想吓坏我吗？
好吧，坚持住。
所以，我躲在水池下面一些钱。
有什么大不了的？
大不了就是你从我这里把它藏！
不，我没有！
那么谁是你的躲呢？
我不知道。这是愚蠢的。你是对的。
我们要离开你想别的话要说了。
IZ，我很抱歉。
IZ！
哦，他妈的。
嘿，这是怎么回事，人呢？
这是怎么回事？
刚准备离开。
那是什么？
我只是想感谢您同意去这一趟。
它不输于我，
牺牲你让这家公司。
我真的很感激。
“为了我的合作伙伴，大卫。世界是你们的。”
- 这是一个从疤面煞星。 - 当然，男人。我记得。
谢谢。
是啊。
呃，嘿嘿，在我走之前，
我只是想...
这是什么？
这是我们的合作伙伴协议。 70-30。
我只是想使它官员。
嗯，当然咯。
- 是个好主意。 - 酷。
男子八周他妈的在阿尔巴尼亚。
IZ是要恨我一辈子。
不，她是怎么回事，每天吸你的公鸡一年。
因为我们是做上的3000万$的边缘。
是啊，男人。
去粉碎它。
多谢兄弟。
尼斯。
嘿，你已经达到了IZ。你知道该怎么做。
来吧，IZ。不要打断我这个样子。
我在阿尔巴尼亚，在酒店。
左侧的数字和你妈妈。
如果你能请你只给我回电话
因为我真的很想念你。好的？
我爱你。
再见。
早上好，伙计。
嘿，巴什基姆。
哦，我给你Kolonat。这是我们的麦当劳。
是啊，我很好。但是感谢。
我们现在去上班？
嗯。不不不。我说我需要两辆卡车。
是啊，你刚刚得到了一个在这里现在。
是啊。你看，我有一架货机坐在机场。
对，我知道。我知道。
嘿，让我叫你马上回来。
嘿，别！停，停！
抱起来，抱起来，抱起来！嘿，把它们关掉！
什么他妈的是什么？
你从哪里得到的？
哟！这是怎么回事？
嘿，伙计，我们得到了一个问题。
- 你在哪？ - 我在丽芙，兄弟。
试图一鼓作气谁是我的桌边等着我一些古巴小鸡。
为什么，我们怎么得了？
让我说清楚。我在阿尔巴尼亚，现在冻结我的屁股。
你在丽芙，试图得到下岗？
大卫，这是凌晨1:00在这里。
我吹了一些蒸气。
是啊，凌晨1:00时你应该在办公室
因为这是他妈的一天中在每一个国家，我们做的生意。
你看，我们得到的AK弹药问题。
- 什么样的问题？ - 这是中国人。
中国，兄弟？这是什么意思，甚至，中国人吗？
这意味着它从中国的。
你在说什么？我在那里，我看到了弹药。
我们都做到了。
是啊，你看，我不知道该怎么告诉你。
他们在性交我们。好的？我们被耍了。
坚持，稍等。你怎么知道它是中国人吗？
有每个箱子他妈的中国文字。
相信我，这是中国人。
是啊。
亨利，什么他妈的！
我们一直在找你两天！
这是埃夫拉伊姆和大卫。
我们有一个严重的问题，他妈的。
我在听。
该AK弹药，这是中国人。
什么，你觉得谁的阿富汗人越来越
塔利班狂涨给他们的地方弹药来自一个狗屎？
没有，但五角大楼确实。
亨利，你知道我们不能用中国人！
美国有对中国的禁运。
你有你的男孩向我们展示阿尔巴尼亚的弹药在整个国家一箱。
对不起，没有任何人阻止你检查其他箱子？
你甚至懒得问原产国是？
谁他妈的会问这个？
亨利，我盯着100万发
中国非法弹药的你卖给我们。
那么，我们应该怎么办？
做你他妈的工作！
美国政府希望寻找其他方式。
不要给他们一个理由不这样做。
虽然你在它，学习之间的差异
“我们有一个问题”和“你有问题。”
他妈的！
我们被性交。弹药是不值钱
我被困在阿尔巴尼亚试图拼凑新的供应商
来自全国各地东欧。
神圣的狗屎。
什么他妈的你在这里干什么，伙计？
我有一个大的想法。
你怎么在我的房间里得到什么？
他们让我进去。
我是一个值得信赖的人。
他们不仅让我，他们给我带来了客房服务。
无论如何，我有一个大他妈的主意。
是吗？那是什么？
如果我们重新包装什么？
重新包装什么？
子弹！
如果我们重新包装他们呢？
亿发？
大卫，这是可以做到。
想想吧。我们也将节省运费的财富。
我们换了所有的大，重型木箱
光纸箱。
是的，但它仍然是中国的弹药。
看看这条毛巾。好的？
土耳其。土耳其制造。
不再。现在是阿尔巴尼亚的毛巾。
这只是中国如果包装说，这是中国人。
是啊。但是，我的意思是，这也是非法他妈的，男人。
我们有两个选择。
我们要么重新包装这个狗屎，并把它关闭
或者我们可以从$ 300亿的交易走开。
您想做什么？
当你把它像有真的只有一个选项。
我们的司机巴什基姆把我们介绍给他的朋友
谁拥有拳击和存储公司出地拉那。
这是恩维尔。我和他一起长大。
很高兴见到你，恩维尔。
你也是。巴什基姆告诉我一些关于你的情况。
是啊，你看，简单地说，我们有一个体重问题。
我们运送弹药量大
从阿尔巴尼亚到阿富汗。
现在，它的包装重罐
里面大木箱。
我们希望做什么
对那些子弹转移到塑料袋
然后把那些在双壁，
瓦楞纸箱。
你知道那些是什么？
嗯，当然咯。是什么原因？
我们只是告诉你。
什么他妈的这个国家是什么呢？
原包装，这是太重了。
太多的板条箱。我们需要简化。
好的。有多少箱？
很多。它的100万发子弹。
了解。但究竟有多少实际的箱子？
我们有68520箱。
我已经看到了。
这他妈的疯了。
完成。
因此50名男子，八个星期。
我能为$ 100,000做到这一点。
100000美元？
是啊。
- 给我们一秒钟。 - 是啊。一秒钟，请。
好的。我会很认真地谈。
这是很难不笑。
我的意思是，不仅是这家伙保存整个交易，
但重新包装的所有弹药
我们将由近300万$增加我们的利润空间。
我们应该从哪里得到共进晚餐吗？
有这个地方的酒店。这是相当不错的。
好的。好了，继续前进。
好吧，成交。
它甚至比我们想象的要好。
我们在交易清淡纸箱重木箱。
8盎司罐装塑料袋。
通过重新包装的弹药，
我们会被180吨减轻我们的整体负载。
180他妈的吨！
这意味着使用更轻的飞机燃烧更少的燃油更少的航班。
所有加起来更多的钱给我们。
在2007年12月8日，
AEY交付了第500万发
阿富汗军队。
它进行得非常顺利。
来吧，只要说一次，亲爱的。来吧。
说“达达”。说“达达”。
我们真的得走了，大卫。
不，嘿嘿，五分钟，好吗？请？
我们约吃饭。我妈妈的等待。
云裳，挥手告别爸爸。嗯。
再见，艾拉。
圣诞节快乐。我爱你。
嘿，你可以给她你的妈妈，这样我们可以谈一下吗？
我很抱歉，大卫。
我们会打电话给你几天。好的？
再见。
嘿，这是大卫。
兄弟，你想听到的东西完全搞砸了？
圣诞快乐，埃夫拉伊姆。
这是圣诞节？
这就是为什么没有人在这里。
我正要火了整个办公室。
不管怎样，当我在那里，
我是说我们的孩子，巴什基姆。
你知道他的叔叔
在阿尔巴尼亚国防部的作品？
不，我不知道。
好吧，他的确。
所以我说，“你知道什么是对我有意思，巴什基姆？
“我很好奇，想知道亨利付出的AK弹药的阿尔巴尼亚人。”
埃夫拉伊姆？
你知道他发现了？
那个混蛋是付出两年半仙圆。
他向我们收费400％的加价！
是啊。所以呢？我们做同样的事情。
是啊，但是这是我们的合同。
我们几乎失去了它，因为他和他的中国他妈的子弹。
但我们并没有失去它。
这不是问题的关键！
我想弄清楚的方式来削减该口交退出交易。
埃夫拉伊姆，停止。
不，听我说。
我是认真的，伙计。
我们赚钱的，行吗？
他赚钱的，整个事情是他妈的工作。
不要惹它。
我不给他妈的。他抓取我们送行！
你看，我是认真的，好吗？
我要上下一班机离开这里，如果你拉的狗屎。
哇。兄弟，你不用威胁我。
好吧？我是你的合作伙伴。
是的，它并不总是这样的。
我发现这个交易。而我在这里
做所有的工作，你是在迈阿密试图破坏它。
我怎么破坏呢？
通过尝试过他妈的亨利，你他妈的在其他人的方式。
你是对的。亨利的合作伙伴。
他是我们得到了这笔交易的原因。
我只是寻找出我们，我把它太远。
不出汗，兄弟。我将离开单干。
谢谢。
我们不能把我们的运气这个狗屎，伙计。
好吧，我会尽快和你谈谈。再见。
哇。什么他妈的？嘿。
他妈的！停止。
停止！我不明白！
你现在明白了么？
是啊。是。
难道你真的认为你可以把我从我自己的交易？
请。
他妈的。
大卫，我们需要谈谈。
现在是不是一个好时机。
我尚未支付。
你什么意思？像月？
永远。
您尚未支付什么？
你的伴侣不回电话。
我的球员需要支付。
他们将停止工作。
大卫，我知道真正的原因
要重新包装的弹药。
好吧，你看，恩维尔。听我说。
我得马上飞到迈阿密。我马上就回来一个星期。
但是，我答应你，我要去的第一件事情做的时候我的土地
为确保你得到你的钱有线，好吗？
好的。
大卫。
机场，我们走吧。
你看，我的飞行晚了。下周我会回来的。
她说，她的丈夫没有回家，昨晚。
好吧，你要我做什么？
她很担心。它不喜欢他。
告诉她，我不知道她的丈夫。
谁是你的丈夫吗？
巴什基姆。
没有人能从巴什基姆再次听到。
他们从来没有发现一张纸条，他们从来没有发现一具尸体。
他刚掉下来的星球。
我当时阿尔巴尼亚完成。
我从来没有回去。
你好。
嘿。
我去了阿尔巴尼亚的原因是分装弹药中国
所以我们可以掩饰它，并把它卖给了美国政府。
这听起来是非法的。
它是。但是我完了。
我发誓，无论我的余生会发生什么
我永远不会再骗你。
嗯，嗯。
我爱你那么多，IZ。
发生了什么事你的鼻子？
我当时阿尔巴尼亚歹徒绑架。
- 我认为这是坏了。 - 哦，我的上帝。
我想我会回去做按摩师。
可以吗？
是。
它总是好的。
嘿，你回来了。
哇！
兄弟，你在做什么了？发生了什么事，你的脸？
这是一个已经在阿富汗的交易提供的一切。
我希望我的削减。我出去了。
你在说什么？
他把枪他妈的我的头，伙计。
谁，亨利？
你说，你要不要管它。
哦，他妈的。
我搞砸了。
我完了，埃夫拉伊姆。
你看，你不用回去。
我聘请了这个新家伙，伊万。
- 他会讲阿尔巴尼亚人。 - 我受够了。
什么，你以为我只是GOT 4百万美元奠定左右？
我已经想通了。
我要对美元40美分。
是的，我认为它经历了太多。
这个怎么样？
如何对美元零美分？
让我提醒你，我们有合同。
他妈的你的合同！
如果我问你我造的房子，
你不干构建我一半的房子后，你觉得我欠你一半的钱？
这是一个笑话他妈的，大卫？
你有两个星期。否则，你会从我的律师听到。
谁，沃伦？
你说的是沃伦？他是我的律师了。
我介绍给他。
他妈的沃伦。
他妈的！
AEY。我怎么可能会引导你的电话？
我们吵架。
与家人扑灭，
与我们的商业伙伴争取。
有时候，我们与我们的朋友而战。
如果上帝在这里，
我们很可能与他拼了。
埃夫拉伊姆有一个沉重的心脏上发生了什么。
没有进攻，拉尔夫，但我不知道你见过真正的埃夫拉伊姆。
他是一个复杂的年轻人。
但他只是想坐下来谈谈。
找到一个公平的解决方案。
他问我来调解。
让我来帮你，大卫。
我只是不知道如果我准备好了。
好吧，他在这里。
嗨！哥们儿。
很高兴见到你。
对不起，事情变得如此疯狂。
是啊。我也是。
你有什么，亲爱的？
我就喝杯咖啡。谢谢。
我想过了很多。
而且我不希望你从这个空手走开。
凉。
因此，我不得不沃伦起草了遣散协议。
我认为这是很公平的。
我准备给你钱了50K，每年在接下来的四年。
200盛大？
这是一个他妈的笑话，男人呢？
这就是你调解的意思？
平心而论，从没有
合伙协议，事先没有合同。
是啊。我有东西比一个合作协议更好。
我有证据。
我离开阿尔巴尼亚前，我把一切。
什么他妈的。
我们所伪造的文件，重新包装的照片。
- 大卫！ - 重新包装？
- 他没告诉你吗？ - 大卫！
哦，是的，我们采取了钱，你给了我们，
我们买了100万发中国非法弹药，
那么，我们重新包装，并将其出售给美国军方。
是啊，我们做了$ 8个万做，混蛋。
小心，埃夫拉伊姆。
我们告诉拉尔夫我们只对一个做$ 3百万。
等等，现在怎么办？
他每月向您发送虚假会计报告。
- 噢，滚开。 - 我让他们在我的笔记本电脑。
现在你要做的仅仅是狗屎。
真？因为我一直的一切，你他妈的哑巴！
我甚至有我们Photoshop处理的银行对账单复印件
并送到政府。
获得他妈的离开这里。
我可以埋葬你。
我们。
我觉得你的意思是说，
你可以把我们埋葬。
因为任何暗示我，
暗示你。
- 埃夫拉伊姆，等待。 - 不不不。
我来到这里，准备今天向您支付$ 200000。
现在，我还没有去支付早餐。
哦。发生了什么事在这里？咦？
你好？
我愿与大卫Packouz说话？
- 是啊，这是谁？ - 嗨，大卫。
这是CJ Chivers与纽约时报。
我想知道，如果你有一分钟??的时间谈AEY，
和所谓中国弹药分装。
我不知道你在说什么。
那么，根据我的消息来源，有一个正在进行的调查
在国务院。
我希望得到一些澄清...
大卫，这听起来相当严重。
对，我知道。
也许你应该叫我叔叔。
律师。
哦，我的上帝。好的。
这是一个好主意。
嘿，给我一分钟。我会满足你在大堂的家伙。
你只是获得纽约时报通话？
是啊。
我也是。
要知道，疤面煞星昨晚在电视上，
我看着它，想着我们小时候
我们用来做电影中的线路。
你是我最好的朋友，大卫。
天啊，我真的搞砸这件事，不是吗？
对不起，兄弟。
哇。
你永远不采取行动，伙计？
这意味着什么？
你只要告诉我你以为我想听，
因为纽约时报叫，
而你吓坏了，我可能会说些什么。
承认吧。
我们从来没有最好的朋友。
你只是在玩我最好的朋友的一部分。
是啊。
疤面煞星昨晚甚至没有??在电视上。
你真是一坨屎。
- 他妈的！ - 去你妈的。
- 他妈的。 - 小母狗。
嗯，这为我们节省了旅途。
在所有我们做了违法的狗屎，
所有的谎言，我们告诉政府，
最终，事情确实是我们？
是的，我试图达到美国国防部，请。
埃夫拉伊姆从未支付的箱子家伙。
为了谁做你报案？
之后恩维尔称为五角大楼，
国务院开展了全面调查，
这持续了几个月。
他们破获拉尔夫在他的工作一天中的商店之一。
他被吓坏了，无法做出处理速度不够快。
所有这一切废话关于他想调解埃夫拉伊姆和我之间的停火协议...
这是一个设置。
哦，是的，我们采取了钱，你给了我们，
我们买了100万发中国非法弹药，
那么，我们重新包装，并将其出售给美国军方。
他们把我们死的权利。
这是可悲的。
虽然经历埃夫拉伊姆的电脑，他们甚至发现了一个待办事项中说，
“改头换面中国弹药”。
这个故事今晚有五角大楼官员争先恐后。
两个20多岁的年轻人是怎么降落一个大合同五角大楼？
联邦特工上周逮捕了两人，欺诈他们充电
出售过时的，有缺陷的中国弹药
五角大楼。
埃夫拉伊姆被控超过70联邦罪
并判处四年徒刑。
我认罪，被判处七个月软禁。
大会呼吁阿富汗承包的案例研究
在所有的错与政府的采购过程。
在2022年，AEY将有资格再次竞标美国联邦合同。
怎么样了？
没关系。
如果我想你死了，你早就死了。
我想它会没事的话。
进来。
请问，你的宝宝吗？
这是一个女孩，对不对？
是啊。她是很好的。
我有三个。
所有的女孩。
他们告诉你，它变得更好。
这是不正确的，它会变得更糟。
这就是为什么我喜欢的军火生意。
没有女性。
我想了解阿尔巴尼亚道歉。
我有不好的信息。
所以，你我塞进一辆汽车的后备箱，并错误地在我脸上猛的一炮？
是啊。
我不是一个坏人，但在某些情况下，
我不得不问自己，
什么会坏男人吗？
我很欣赏你离开我的名字从你的证词。
我真的不明白了一个道理，包括它。
是的，但仍。
我可以问你一个问题吗？
当然。
当我们在拉斯维加斯见面了在酒杯表，
是巧合？
你有什么感想？
我能问你一个问题吗？
我在阿尔巴尼亚司机失踪。
你知道他怎么了？
这是我的一块在阿富汗的交易结束。
这是给你的。
没有更多的问题。
Please! Please!
I'm sorry, I don't speak Albanian!
Stop! I don't understand!
Do you understand now?
That's a Jericho 941 pointed at my head.
You can get one on the black market for $300.
Yeah.
It is a very reliable weapon.
My name is David Packouz.
And I'm an international arms dealer.
What do you know about war?
They'll tell you it's about patriotism, democracy
or some shit about the other guy hating our freedom.
But you want to know what it's really about?
What do you see?
A kid from Arkansas doing his patriotic duty to defend his country?
I see a helmet, fire-retardant gloves,
body armor, and an M16.
I see $17,500.
That's what it costs to outfit one American soldier.
Over two million soldiers
fought in Iraq and Afghanistan.
It cost the American taxpayer $4.5 billion each year
just to pay the air conditioning bills
for those wars.
And that's what war is really about.
War is an economy.
Anybody who tells you otherwise
is either in on it or stupid.
But I didn't know that yet.
Back then, I didn't know anything.
You can't park here.
Hey, man. I just got a client at 2150, Mr. Shore.
I'm a few minutes early.
Yeah? It's a gated community.
You still can't park here.
You probably shouldn't smoke that here, either.
Okay. Thanks.
There's a lot I could say about this period in my life
that would give context to this story.
I could tell you how
I dropped out of college after one semester.
- How's that left quad doing?  - It's still sore.
Had a falling out with my parents.
How I either quit or got fired from six different jobs.
- That's it.  - All right. There we go.
But looking back I think the most important thing to understand is
I was completely lost.
Sorry. It fell.
That's okay, Gary.
I was 22 years old
massaging rich dudes in Miami Beach for 75 bucks an hour.
But I'd had enough.
It was time to change shit up.
And I had a big idea.
My plan was to sell quality bed sheets wholesale
to all the retirement homes in South Florida.
And there were hundreds of them.
- It feels really soft.  - It should.
It's Egyptian cotton, 400 thread count.
I mean, it's pretty much top of the line for institutional use.
I don't know. It seems excessive.
Well, at $29 per unit, it's far from excessive.
David, do you know the average age of a resident here at Hilldale?
Um, no, I don't.
- Eighty-two years old.  - Wow.
Have you ever seen the skin on an 82-year-old man?
Have you ever felt it?
Yeah. Actually, I'm a certified massage therapist
and a lot of my clients are elderly.
Then you should know.
These sheets,
it would be like wrapping a lizard in cashmere.
Would you do that?
Would you wrap a lizard in cashmere?
I guess not.
Then why would you expect me to?
My nephew.
He's good, right?
I'd sunk my entire life savings into 65 cases of premium bed sheets
but I overlooked one crucial factor.
No one really cares about old people.
Why don't you just sell them back?
It doesn't work like that. I bought them in bulk.
I'm so fucked.
You're not fucked.
Pete's fucked.
He's dead.
Holy shit. Is that Efraim?
Yeah.
I thought he was still in LA.
Me too.
- He was a great friend.  - Thank you.
He looks so tan.
Efraim Diveroli was my best friend growing up.
But I hadn't seen him since he was shipped off to live with his uncle in 10th grade.
I think our parents wanted to keep us as far apart as possible.
There is no table of contents in the Book of Life.
We don't know if we're at the beginning of a new chapter, or the end of a story.
Which is why we must be grateful every time the page turns.
Did you come back just for this?
Fuck no! I barely knew Pete.
I was hoping to see you here.
You know your mom wouldn't give me your number?
What, did you call my house?
No, I was fucking her.
She still hates me, huh?
Yeah, most likely.
I missed you, bro.
Yeah, me too.
Let's go for a ride.
Uh...
I can't. I got a client at 4:00.
Fuck that shit. Cancel it.
Your boy's back in town.
Come on!
So, what happened with LA, man?
Why did you move back?
Oh, you know I was working for my uncle, right?
Yeah, I heard that you were, like, a gun dealer or something.
Pretty much. I mean,
we'd buy seized weapons at police auctions and resell them on the Internet.
Cool.
It was cool until my uncle scumbagged me over 70 grand.
Holy shit. Seventy grand?
Whatever. Fuck him. I made a bunch of money.
I decided I'd come back to Miami, start up my own shop.
Cool.
Yo, where's this guy live?
It's, like, five more minutes. You got somewhere you gotta be?
No.
All right. So, I can't figure out which is worse.
The fact that you sell bed sheets to old age homes
or that you jerk guys off for money.
For the record, I'm a licensed massage therapist, okay?
Totally legit.
Okay. But at the end, the guys have to come, right?
Like, on your chest or whatever?
You know what? Fuck you.
Fuck you, buddy.
Bro, do you remember the last time we went to buy weed together?
Of course I do. It was fucking traumatic.
Yeah, but do you remember the next day, when we walked into school
and everybody knew that we got arrested?
Yeah, we were gangsters, bro.
We thought we ran South Beach.
We did run yeshiva.
We didn't take shit from anyone.
Yeah, I miss that.
You miss yeshiva?
No, I miss
not taking shit from anyone.
Yo!
He out. You looking for weed?
Depends. You got good shit?
Put it this way. I sell him his shit.
What's up with this nigga, man?
Cool. Can you do an ounce?
Yeah, no sweat. Three bills.
Three hundred. I like it.
You get the better price when you come direct to the distributor.
I guess so.
All right.
Yeah, so, she opened the door.
And I'm like, "Yo. Chill. I ain't about that drama."
You know what I mean?
"I know you got another nigga in the crib."
What's up?
What?
Can I get the shit?
What shit?
I just gave you $300 for some weed.
Any of you niggas ever seen this motherfucker before?
I ain't seen shit.
Man, get the fuck out of here.
- All right. All right, okay.  - Yeah, yeah.
This white boy wild.
Parachute pants.
Looking like Jay Leno and shit.
Look like he going to church.
Yo, yo, hold up, hold up, man.
- What the fuck.  - Shit!
Come on! Where's everybody going?
I thought we were gonna hang out.
What a bunch of assholes.
What the fuck was that? Are you crazy?
It's cool, bro.
I have a Class 3 Firearms license.
- Huh?  - Come on, get in.
I know another dealer nearby.
It's weird. We were the same age, but I always looked up to Efraim.
When life kicked me, I stayed down.
But not Efraim. He kicked back.
Mr. President, we want to thank you
for visiting us here today.
We are honored to be serving our country,
and proud to welcome you,
our wartime Commander in Chief...
- Hey.  - Hey, sweetie.
How was the funeral?
It was amazing.
Oh, my God. You're so stoned, aren't you?
Huh? What?
You just described a funeral as "amazing."
What? No. The funeral was really sad.
Yeah, everyone was totally bummed out.
But I ran into my friend from growing up.
The guy I told you about. Efraim Diveroli?
The one you got arrested with?
Yeah. I mean, we did some other stuff too, but...
Anyway, he just moved back to Miami.
That's great, right?
Yeah. I'm supposed to swing by his office tomorrow.
We're gonna grab lunch.
- Okay.  - Are you hungry?
- Hmm?  - I'm so hungry.
- We don't have much here.  - Oh.
- I mean, we have pizza.  - Really?
- And nachos.  - We have nachos?
And ice cream.
Wait, what? We never have ice cream.
You're fucking with me, aren't you?
That is so mean.
That was so easy.
Hello?
Hello, Mr. Borstein. This is David Packouz.
You told me to call today at 11:00.
I have those bed sheets with me, and I would love for you to take a look.
Uh, sir, if you give me the chance
I am confident that your residents
will appreciate the difference.
It's an expense we can't justify, and we're just not interested.
Uh-huh.
Okay, well, thank you for your time.
Yeah, this is contract specialist
Lindsey Michaels from Army Command, Picatinny.
That's right.
Yeah, I sent out a solicitation for some 249s for Basra
and we seem to have misplaced your paperwork.
Great. So if you can go ahead and just re-email me those numbers.
Actually, you know what? On second thought,
we're about to make a decision on those RFPs.
Why don't you go ahead and just give me your bid while I got you here on the phone?
Uh-huh.
And does that include mags?
Great. Yes, sir.
You keep supplying the guns, we'll keep killing the bad guys.
God bless you.
What a fucking tool. What's up, bro?
Yo, what's up, man? What was that all about?
Oh, that was me impersonating an army officer.
Really? What for?
To find out what my competitor's bidding on a contract.
It's fucking genius.
I thought that you said you sold, like, seized weapons to gun nuts on the Internet.
Not anymore.
Now I only sell to one gun nut.
Oh, yeah? Which one?
The U.S. Military, motherfucker.
Wanna do a bong hit?
Pretty sick, huh?
So what, you sell these things to the Pentagon?
I sell all kinds of shit to the Pentagon.
Guns, bullets, body armor.
Last week, I shipped 400 gas masks to American Special Forces in Iraq.
No shit.
How long you been doing this for?
Two, three months.
And you make good money?
Oh! Fuck, man.
Put it this way. I did over 200K in the past eight weeks.
And I'm only telling you that because you're my boy.
I'm not bragging.
Holy shit.
Yeah. Check this out.
Fed Biz Opps stands for Federal Business Opportunities.
Think eBay, but for war.
- They buy tanks on here?  - Bro, they buy everything on here.
It was crazy.
The government had a public website
containing every military contract currently up for bidding.
But I skip the big ticket items, and look for the small-ball shit
that giant defense contractors ignore.
Everybody's fighting over the same pie.
But they're ignoring the crumbs.
I live on crumbs, like a rat.
And when you're dealing with the Pentagon, crumbs are worth millions.
These listings seemed to go on forever.
And according to Efraim, they did.
Thanks, man.
So, I don't get it.
If there's an entire defense industry,
why would the Pentagon want to buy anything from you?
They don't want to, they have to.
Remember Little League?
How, at the end of the season, they'd give out that big MVP trophy
and that one kid would always win it?
Yeah, Evan Talbot.
Right. But then, one year, somebody's mom complained?
Then they had to give everybody a little trophy so they wouldn't feel bad?
Even that fat retarded kid, Robbie Friedman, got one.
That's kind of like what's happening here.
I'm still confused, man.
The Pentagon fucked up when they were rebuilding the Iraqi Army.
They gave all these no-bid contracts to Cheney's boys, and they got caught.
So Bush started this initiative to level the playing field
and now every Pentagon purchase, every gun, every grenade,
every bullet, gets offered to small businesses for bidding.
And sure, the big dogs still get the big trophies.
But the Pentagon's got to give little trophies
to all the Robbie Friedmans of the world.
So, basically, you're a fat retarded kid.
Bro, I'm the fattest and most retarded.
In a speech today, President Bush said that contrary to reports
he has no plans to attack Iran.
The President said, "That's ridiculous.
"We didn't even have plans when we attacked Iraq. "
David.
Yeah?
Remember a few weeks ago, in the car on the way home from my mom's house?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Well, this happened.
How the fuck are you going to feed a baby?
Have you even thought about this?
What are you going to do?
Jerk men off the rest of your life?
Yeah, that's the plan. I'm gonna feed my kid by jerking men off.
Sorry.
Okay, good. Well, at least you thought it through.
It's not funny.
Dude, I am so fucked.
I think you should come work for me.
What are you talking about?
Seriously, I need the help.
David, look at me.
Bush opened the floodgates in Iraq.
It's a fucking gold rush.
That's really nice of you, Efraim.
Fuck nice! Who cares about nice?
I've been looking to bring somebody on for a while now.
The problem is, I don't trust anyone.
But you're my boy.
I mean, no offense, but I'm against this war.
Me and Iz are going to rallies and signing petitions.
Yeah, dude, I'm against the war too.
I fucking hate Bush.
But this isn't about being pro-war.
The war is happening.
This is about being pro-money.
The more Efraim talked, the more it made sense.
Besides, compared to my other prospects,
this was the chance of a lifetime.
My only issue was, what would I tell Iz?
I think it's a great idea.
So I lied.
You know I've always believed in this business.
I told her that Efraim had great contacts in the government.
And instead of selling bed sheets
to penny-pinching retirement homes
we'd now be selling sheets to the free-spending,
overfunded U.S. Military.
It's genius.
I had to lie. Iz hated the war.
She had two cousins serving in Iraq.
She also hated the mountain of bed sheets that were taking up half our apartment.
I spent the next six weeks in a crash course on arms dealing.
The Herstal 556 light machine gun.
Belgian, but made under license in lots of places.
When it came to this shit, Efraim knew everything.
Makes, models, weights, where it was made.
Remember, there's been an arms embargo against China since Tiananmen Square.
And if there was an angle to be played, he knew about that too.
You have to read between the lines with this stuff.
All the money is made between the lines.
I'd spend my entire day scouring the government's website,
searching for overlooked contracts that we could squeeze our way into.
Hey, I think I got something.
Hey, Georgia, I gotta call you back.
And then, in the middle of the night
we'd be back in the office, working the phones.
Forging relationships
with weapon manufacturers all over Eastern Europe.
No, David Packouz from AEY.
I told Iz we were doing conference calls with sheet suppliers in Pakistan.
They called guys like us war dogs.
Bottom feeders who make money off of war
without ever stepping foot on the battlefield.
It was meant to be derogatory, but we kinda liked it.
You fucking scumbag piece of shit!
Drown, motherfucker, drown!
Very nice.
Ralph Slutsky was Efraim's silent partner.
He was a local businessman
who owned 14 dry cleaners all across Miami.
Why didn't anybody tell me the mister is broken?
Ralph put up the money to back the deals in exchange for 25% of the company.
Or at least what he thought was 25%.
We're doing God's work, Ralph.
We really are.
You know, every Jew owes a debt to Israel.
In my mind, this is not a metaphorical debt.
Ralph was under the impression that Efraim was an observant Jew
who only dealt arms as a means
to protect Israel from her enemies.
Beautifully said.
Did you happen to catch last Friday's Torah portion?
- One of my favorites.  - Same here.
It reminds me so much of this story I once read.
About a young man traveling to Pinsk.
And that was Efraim's genius.
He would figure out who someone wanted him to be
and he would become that person.
Ah!
And he's got, like, 20,000 of them.
Great. Where did you find this guy?
You remember Victor in the Ukraine?
Yeah, the one with the Mk3s?
Yeah. He turned me on to this company in Cyprus.
It's run by this guy, Henry Girard.
Henry Girard?
Yeah, you know him?
You spoke to Henry Girard?
A couple of times. Why? Who is he?
Dude, for the last 20 years, this guy has basically supplied
both sides of every conflict on the planet.
He's a fucking animal.
Really? Why is he calling me?
Because he's a fucking animal.
It's all money and it all matters.
Hey, mami, where are you going?
I'm trying to find my friends.
You want to make some money?
Excuse me?
I'll give you $1,000 right now
if we fast forward to our third date.
What does that even mean?
It means we just had a great dinner, maybe met your friends for some drinks
and now you're about to blow me in my car.
Can we just get right to that part?
Who the fuck are you?
Efraim Diveroli.
That's my best friend, David.
And we're international arms dealers.
But you already know that
because we're on our third date.
- What's going on?  - Nothing, bro.
I'm about to get out of here with my girl.
What the fuck, man!
Oh, my God.
That guy was not fucking around.
Yeah, you probably should have picked a different girl.
Fuck that, it almost worked.
Hey, do you remember when you fought Eric Moscowitz in sixth grade?
Yeah, he did that windmill thing with his arms.
That was the sickest. He was unbeatable.
You remember that shit?
That's it.
Dude, he would have killed me if you didn't jump in.
Probably. Mmm.
Hey, I never said "thank you."
For everything.
Come on, you know how much you've helped me out lately.
It's cool. You don't have to make it weird, all right?
Hey, can we order some food?
Mami, come on. I could have gone to Cuba and back.
Met the family, grabbed a couple sandwiches.
I'd be done by now.
Hello?
Yes, sir. Sorry, I wasn't expecting a work call this late.
Right, of course. It's 9:00 a.m. in Baghdad.
Who is it?
That's great news, Captain Santos.
Yes, sir.
We're going to get right on that.
Thank you. Bye.
What?
We just got the Beretta deal.
Get the fuck out of here.
I swear to God.
The Beretta deal was massive.
It was 10 times bigger than anything we'd closed so far.
This was next level shit.
That's what I'm fucking talking about!
That's real money, motherfucker! Fuck!
Do you realize we're going to make 600K
on this fucking thing?
Holy shit.
David, your 30% is $180,000.
Holy fucking shit!
It was amazing.
I'd been working with Efraim for two months
and was already about to make more money
than a lifetime of massages.
Listen.
What is that?
That's your baby's heartbeat.
Wow.
Can you believe how fast it is?
- Is that normal?  - Totally normal.
Fetuses have a much faster heart rate than we do.
Look.
So, you guys want to know the sex?
We keep going back and forth on it.
- What do you think?  - Um...
This is work. I have to take it.
I'm so sorry.
This is David.
This is Captain Santos in Baghdad
checking on the delivery status of my Berettas.
Captain, good to hear from you.
Yes, we are on target. All good.
Great. I was worried
those guns were coming direct out of Italy.
Absolutely. They are, sir.
Packouz, please tell me
you're aware of the legislation the Italians passed last week.
The one banning all arms shipments to Iraq.
I had no clue what he was talking about.
But this was a huge fucking problem.
Berettas are an Italian gun.
Made and manufactured in Italy.
Uh...
Of course.
I am. I've been on the phone
for the last three days, making other arrangements.
Great. That's what I wanted to hear.
Iraqi police force is depending on you.
Well, you tell them AEY has got them covered.
- Outstanding.  - Thanks, Captain. Talk soon.
Everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah, everything's fine.
What happened? We done already?
Yeah. Guess what?
It's a girl.
Baby.
Okay. At least I hit something.
Seriously, what the fuck are we going to do?
Relax, bro.
Should I just call him back and tell him the truth?
When does telling the truth ever help anybody?
Efraim, we can't dick around with this guy
and then not deliver.
We're going to deliver.
I already figured it out.
We use Jordan.
Jordan Goldfarb?
Jordan...
Jordan the country.
It shares a border with Iraq. It's a U.S. ally.
And most importantly, there's no embargo.
Okay, so what do we tell the Italians?
Fuck them! As far as they're concerned
they're sending 5,000 Berettas to a country they have no issue with.
All we have to do is ship the guns
from Jordan to Baghdad.
It's called circumvention.
Is that legal?
It's not illegal.
Want to try?
How did that charity thing go?
It was 5K, right?
It was supposed to be a 5K.
Uh, I finished about 1 K of it.
So, I should probably return four-fifths of the money.
So, Andrew told me
you and Efraim are working together now?
Really?
Yeah, I told her about the sheet thing.
Yeah. Efraim has some contacts with the government.
So we're just combining forces right now.
Yeah, just... Just be careful with him.
- Emily, don't.  - What?
How do you mean?
Well, his cousin, Rebecca, is an old friend of mine.
We went to camp together.
And she told me that he stole $70,000 from her father.
Whoa, really?
That's interesting.
I actually heard it was the other way around.
That his uncle is the one who stole the money from him.
See? You don't know.
Everyone has their own version of a story.
No, I'm pretty certain.
Their whole family stopped talking to him over it.
Yo! Why aren't you answering your phone?
Hey, what's up, man?
Fuck is this?
Everyone, this is David's business partner, Efraim.
- Hey, man.  - Hey, man.
Bro, could I talk to you outside for a minute?
- It's urgent.  - Yeah, of course.
And for the record, I'm also his best friend,
so probably should have been invited to whatever this is.
Look, these are her friends. This is her dinner party.
Rosen is her friend now? That Jew fuck?
Trust me, you don't want to be here.
I don't want to be here, all right?
Now, what's going on?
Jordanian customs seized our Berettas.
- What? Why?   - I don't fucking know, David.
I dropped out of high school before they covered international diplomacy.
- Who's that?  - Fuck, it's Santos.
He knows!
Pick it up, I want to listen.
- Pick... Pick up the fucking phone.  - This is David.
Yeah, I just heard my guns are being held up in Jordan.
Captain Santos, yes, there's been a slight hiccup.
What are they even doing in Jordan?
Not to worry.
They're in a hangar in Amman. Totally safe.
My team and I are working on a solution right now.
You didn't answer my question.
What the fuck are my guns doing in Jordan?
Captain Santos, this is Efraim Diveroli.
President of AEY, sir.
David has apprised me of the situation and we are looking at options as we speak.
Options? What kind of options?
Well, are you familiar with the Corvus TP1 9?
That's Brazilian and it's shit.
Contract says Berettas, I want Berettas.
Sir, I need you to work with us a little on this.
Let me get this straight.
I'm in the ass crack of the world, defending your freedom.
And I got to work with you shit bags?
Look, I don't know
if those Berettas are really in Amman or if you're just trying to goose your profits
like every other piece of shit in your miserable, rat-fuck profession.
Either way, you're endangering my mission.
I'm shutting you down.
I'm canceling you for cause.
Getting canceled for cause was a death sentence.
It meant we would never win another contract.
Captain, please do not do that.
I know you're upset.
But from one Christian to another
my wife and I are having serious financial problems.
Our son, Lucas, is in the hospital.
Medical bills are through the roof.
If you do this, it'll ruin me. It'll ruin my family.
As God as my witness,
I will get you your guns.
Hello?
What a fucking piece of shit! Do you believe this fucking guy?
- Fuck.  - What's going on?
What guns, David?
Are you fucking kidding me?
You told me you guys were selling bed sheets.
Yeah, and I also told you that we're selling other stuff too.
I thought you meant pillows!
Look, I can't support a kid by giving massages.
Okay? And nobody was buying the bed sheets.
No, David, you lied to me.
Because I know how you feel about the war.
I thought we both felt that way!
I'm five months pregnant!
And it's a problem if I can't trust the man
I'm having a baby with!
- Of course you can trust me.  - Really?
Because five minutes ago, I didn't even know you were an arms dealer!
I'm not an arms dealer.
What we do is perfectly legal.
We work for the government. We're middlemen.
We don't touch the guns, we don't see the guns.
We never even leave the office.
Hey, sorry to interrupt. It's time sensitive.
David, do you have a passport?
What? Yeah, why?
We have to go to Jordan. Like, ASAP.
Straighten this shit out.
We gotta talk, whatever, okay?
Yeah.
Yo, you window or aisle?
- Excuse me, sorry.  - Yeah, we just landed.
- Excuse me.  - The Embassy call?
Excuse me. Okay, bye.
- Sorry, kind of an emergency.  - Excuse me. Sorry.
Don't worry, I have to go first. I'm American.
I'm sorry.
The American Embassy offered little to no help
in dealing with the Ministry of Customs.
So we took matters into our own hands.
He says your permit has expired
and that you can't fly your crates out of Jordan without one.
Yeah, we know. That's why we're here.
Look, we were told that you know people in the government,
that maybe you can help us out.
He says it will take six weeks to get a new permit.
Yeah, that's the issue. We don't have six weeks.
We need our guns today.
Look, I don't want to come off as the ugly American here.
And maybe I don't understand the rituals of your culture
but this feels like the moment
where we are supposed to offer him a gift, am I correct?
- You are correct.  - All right.
$1,400 U.S. Cool?
Cool, man.
Could have just started with that, you know, saved all this bullshit.
I like your shades.
Tell him I'll give him 100 bucks for those shades.
Tell him in gibberish.
No way. Alligator.
Yeah, I know. I...
It's Lacoste. It's actually a crocodile.
I like fancy shit, that's my thing.
Tell him.
For three days, we didn't hear anything.
It was ridiculous.
Our entire business was riding on the word of an 11-year-old translator.
Motherfucker! He ripped us off!
We don't know that yet.
No! I know what it feels like to fuck somebody.
I also know what it feels like to get fucked by somebody.
And we just got fucked.
You need to chill out.
How am I supposed to chill out, David?
We're in a Muslim country, I can't even get a blowjob!
It's embarrassing!
It's chaos here! Fuck!
Yeah.
Right now?
We're coming down.
That was Aladdin. They're in the lobby.
See that? Come on.
Hold on. Are you fucking kidding me?
What's the problem?
You wanted your guns back, he got you your guns back.
What? No, we said we needed a permit to fly them to Iraq.
Exactly, but you don't need a permit to drive them.
You expect us to drive them to Iraq?
Why not? Marlboro is the best smuggler in all of Jordan.
Who, this?
This is the best smuggler in all of Jordan?
Yeah, he drives to Baghdad three, four times a month.
Efraim, you want to weigh in here?
Yo, how far is it to Baghdad?
- Why are you asking him that?  - 800 kilometers.
And he knows what he's doing?
Efraim, stop.
- 100% the best.  - Come on.
It's like 500 miles. We'll be there by morning.
You seriously want to drive to Baghdad?
David, we're gunrunners.
Let's go run some fucking guns.
Let's go.
Come on.
Hey, seriously, is this safe? Driving to Baghdad?
Yes, very safe.
50-50.
50-50? What, like 50% we live, 50% we die?
Yes. That is why we drive through night.
It is much safer.
How much safer?
50-50.
Bro, what the fuck!
Obviously, he doesn't know what 50-50 means.
Oh, my God.
Hey, what about gas though? It's a long trip, no?
No problem. Petrol free in Iraq.
No kidding.
- Free gas?   - Yeah.
See what I'm talking about? Iraq is dope.
I'm thinking about getting a place there.
Free gas.
Fucking cool, man.
What is that?
What?
You don't see that?
What the fuck?
Hey, why are you slowing down, man?
It's okay, it's okay.
What's okay?
Whoa, whoa. What the fuck, bro?
It's okay. Border.
What, this?
Fuck.
- Jesus.  - Put down.
- Huh?  - Put down.
Whoa, whoa.
Cigarettes.
For you.
Welcome.
It was fucking surreal.
Six months ago, I was a massage therapist in Miami Beach.
And now, here I was, driving a truckload of guns
through the Iraqi desert
with my best friend from junior high.
Marlboro?
Hey, Marlboro?
Bro!
There's a dead body in the gas station!
What the fuck!
Where are we? Where's Marlboro?
Did you not hear what I just said?
There's a fucking dead body in there, man!
Yes, I heard you.
All right, we're in a war zone, bro.
There's dead bodies, relax.
All right, I gotta take a leak.
What?
Be careful.
I'm good, bro. I know how to take a piss, all right?
Shit.
Fuck.
- Hello?  - Hey.
Hey, babe, is everything okay?
Yeah.
What time is it there?
It's, uh, 7:30 in the morning.
Shit, did I wake you?
No, I'm just at the hotel. We're about to have some breakfast.
Listen, I'm not saying I like it,
but I get why you're doing this.
You do?
This whole time I never thought about what you must be going through.
All the pressure you're under.
It's just the lying that kills me.
It makes me feel like I'm in this alone.
No, you're not in this alone.
I need you to know that you can tell me anything, David.
We're partners, remember?
David?
Yeah, I gotta call you right back.
- Is everything okay?  - Yeah, everything's fine.
I'm just going to call you right back, okay?
I love you. Bye.
Efraim!
- What?  - Look!
Marlboro!
Fuck! What the fuck, bro.
Holy shit, they have guns, man!
I know!
Go, go! Come on.
What the fuck! It won't start!
Where the fuck is Marlboro?
- I got it!  - Go! Go!
No, no, no!
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait! No!
Run, motherfucker! Jump in!
Holy shit! They're getting closer. Come on, man. Go!
Go, go!
Come on!
Are you kidding me?
We stopped for gas in Fallujah?
You cheap fuck!
Go!
Fuck you, Marlboro!
Fuck.
Fuck. Fuck.
We're gonna die!
You wanted to drive to Baghdad, you asshole!
They're stopping.
What the fuck? Look.
Holy fuck, bro.
Oh, fuck! All right!
God bless Dick Cheney's America!
Look at this fucking place. Oh, my God.
Excuse me, sir?
What?
There are some guys here to see you.
Some guys?
What kind of guys?
Hey, Marlboro!
Give us a smile, gorgeous.
Let me see those pearly yellows.
You're like an Iraqi Tom Selleck, bro.
You guys are AEY?
Yes, sir. David Packouz.
This is my colleague, Efraim Diveroli.
We spoke on the phone.
I remember.
You drove these?
Through the Triangle of Death?
Fucking A right we did.
Kip, take these boys over to the cage, get them paid.
Right away, sir.
I was wrong about you two.
Great fucking job, boys.
Great fucking job.
Holy shit, the Triangle of Death, bro?
That's right. That's the AEY guarantee, bitch.
We drive through all triangles, including your mom's.
Hey, Kip, snap a photo of us, pal.
All right.
Ready?
- How's my hair?  - It's good, slicked back.
Thank you.
- Got you.  - Let me see it.
Helmut fucking Newton over here.
All right, man.
- Perfect.  - All right, all right.
Let's go get fucking paid.
Holy shit.
Crazy, right? $12.2 billion.
It's all seized from the godfather himself.
You guys call Saddam Hussein the godfather?
Look at all this cash, bro. What would you call him?
$2.8 million.
- Just sign here.  - You got it.
We got a military escort to the airport
and got the fuck out of Baghdad.
There was almost $3 million in cash
stuffed into our Army-issued duffel bags.
You might think after barely surviving Iraq
that we'd be done.
But you'd be wrong.
You see, the Beretta deal put us on the map.
After that, we started killing it.
We bought matching Porsches.
We bought two apartments in the same building.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit, bro.
Oh!
Whoo!
Ralph was so happy with his returns
that he increased his original investment
in AEY by $10 million.
That gave us enough capital to pursue more deals
and expand the company.
Which is exactly what we did.
I cannot stress this enough.
You need to be scouring this website.
Day and night.
It is updated by the minute.
There are tens of thousands of solicitations on this website.
Each one is 40 to 50 pages long.
If you see something interesting,
you bring it to me.
If you bring it to me,
I'll make you rich.
Fact, 18 months ago,
David here was jerking off guys for money.
Actually, that is not a fact.
That is absolutely a fact.
Now he drives a Porsche.
And that's all because of AEY.
Do you have any questions?
Um, I have a question.
What does AEY stand for?
What do you mean? Like morally?
No, I mean what do the letters mean?
That's fucking...
What does IBM stand for? Nothing.
It just... It just sounds professional.
Uh, actually, IBM stands for International Business Machines.
What did you say?
IBM stands for International Business Machines.
Get the fuck out of here.
I'm serious. You're not going to work here.
Get the fuck out of my office, you fucking nerd!
Go!
And for the record, AEY doesn't stand for anything.
Fuck! What a dick.
Does anybody else have any questions?
Sleep. I got her.
All right. All right.
Hi.
I know.
I know. It's okay.
Okay.
What?
360,000 SVD sniper rifles.
1,084,000 GP-30 grenades.
45,000 SKO aviation rockets.
The Pentagon's arming the Afghans for the next 30 years.
They're building a whole army.
Wait, that's got to be a typo.
It's not.
100 million rounds of AK-47 ammo?
Bro, these aren't crumbs.
This is the whole fucking pie.
Among defense contractors,
this would come to be known as the Afghan deal.
It would be the biggest opportunity
AEY would ever see.
We had to go for it.
So, where do you go to arm an entire country?
Vegas X is where military and manufacturers
come together to unveil the latest in warfare.
It's like Comic-Con with grenades.
Sure, most of these guys didn't know who AEY was.
But we saw that as an advantage.
- You got your list?  - Got it.
- You feel good?  - Yeah, I feel pretty good.
You know, this is different than doing business on the phone.
When they look at us, they're going to see two kids.
So we have to show them our balls.
Got it.
We need to be fucking thugs, you understand?
Understood.
All right, good. Let's kill this shit.
But it was a complete disaster.
We quickly learned that
even if we could land the Afghan deal,
it would be a logistical nightmare.
Jerry, good to see you.
To source a deal of this magnitude
would mean piecing together
multiple vendors from all around the world.
Whoa, whoa.
Get out of here.
It would require dozens of shipping outfits
and hundreds of permits.
We need 100 million rounds.
All that could be okay for a major defense contractor.
But not for us.
Honestly, we were out of our league.
Change $10,000.
Any luck today?
Efraim!
What's up, bro?
Where you been? Why aren't you answering your phone?
I'm with a prostitute. What's up?
Okay, you need to get dressed and come with me right now.
All right, uh, give me
38 minutes.
Efraim, Henry Girard is down at the bar, waiting for us.
Get the fuck out of here.
I'm dead serious.
Shit.
Okay.
Henry Girard was a legend among arms dealers.
When they hung Saddam Hussein for crimes against humanity
it was said that Henry sold them the rope.
Hey, Henry, sorry I'm late.
This is my partner I was telling you about.
- Efraim Diveroli.  - Nice to meet you.
It's an absolute pleasure.
Henry has a dinner in 10 minutes,
but I wanted you to hear this firsthand.
I showed him the list and he can help.
Great. With which part?
All of it.
He can fill the whole order.
- The whole order?  - Mmm-hmm.
Even the AK ammo?
Not a problem.
You do know it's 100 million rounds, right?
Henry has contacts in Albania.
Albania?
They spent decades preparing for a Western invasion that never came.
That country is one giant arsenal.
It's all just sitting there.
Tell him the best part.
They're in the process of joining NATO,
so they have to dispose of all of their Soviet era weapons.
They are literally dismantling it and turning it into scrap.
I can get most of the shit for pennies on the dollar.
Now, tell him the other best part.
You're looking at the exclusive agent for the whole fucking thing.
This was the magic bullet.
One supplier who could fill the entire Afghan deal.
This wouldn't just put us in contention.
We might actually win this thing.
Sorry, I have a question.
Sure.
With that kind of hookup
why don't you just bid on the contract yourself?
Full disclosure?
I'm barred from doing any business with the U.S. government.
I'm on a watch list.
Like a terrorist watch list?
Mmm-hmm.
- Got it.  - Wait, what?
Okay, how much for the AK ammo?
- 10 cents a round.  - That's fucking amazing.
And what about shipping?
You can get Ilyushin 76 through Russian pilots.
80K per flight.
I'm sorry, you're on a terrorist watch list?
What the fuck!
Do you work for Homeland Security? Relax, bro.
You two should probably talk this over.
We will. But we are very interested.
Good. My flight leaves tomorrow morning at 10:00.
I can't spend more than 48 hours in this dump.
That's what I always say. Vegas is a two-day town.
I was talking about America.
We're talking exclusive access to a stockpile
of Soviet Bloc non-standard weapons and ammo.
That's going to win this deal for us.
He's on a terrorist watch list!
Whatever. People end up on that list for bringing scissors onto an airplane!
That's not why he's on the list.
Look, the Pentagon wants 100 million rounds of AK-47 ammo
in the middle of a worldwide shortage.
Where do you think they think that's going to come from?
A bunch of shady motherfuckers like that guy.
This is the job.
To do business with the people in places
the U.S. government can't do business with directly.
It's as simple as that.
Fuck!
Hey, boys.
So we discussed it, and we'd like to move forward.
Fantastic. Congratulations.
- But we have to see the merchandise.  - Oh, of course.
On site, in person.
You guys ever been to Albania?
Honestly, until last night
I didn't even know it was a real fucking country.
Oh, it's a beautiful place.
Come on in. I'll call my guy and we'll set it up.
Albania is a lot of things.
But a beautiful place is not one of them.
It took us three separate flights
and 22 hours just to get there.
Henry's people sent a driver
to pick us up at the airport
and the guy would not stop talking.
I fall over, she revive me.
But none of that diminished Efraim's enthusiasm.
He really believed this could be the answer.
Welcome, AEY.
I am Yili Pinari,
head of Albania's largest military export company.
Efraim Diveroli. Good to see you.
This is my business associate, David Packouz.
- Glad to meet you.  - How you doing?
Uh...
Thank you for the sign.
Oh. It's for you.
Yes, I know. I said thank you for the sign.
So, show us what you got.
What is this place?
Storage for the Albanian army.
We have 700 more like it across the country.
You have 700 warehouses like this?
Not just warehouse.
We use church, hospital, school.
Albania is most armed country in the world.
Hey, that's cool. Congrats, bro.
It was like a fucking museum in there.
Most of this shit hadn't seen daylight
since the Cold War.
But that didn't matter to us.
All we cared about was the AK ammo.
It's okay. We have plenty of what you came for.
All these containers are filled with your bullets.
What do you mean, all the bullets are right here?
126 million rounds.
Fuck me.
Yeah. Fuck us all.
How old are these?
30, maybe 40 years. AK-47 bullets
can last forever if properly stored.
Right. Well, how were these stored?
Uh, who gives a fuck how these were stored?
All that matters is they fucking work.
Do they work?
You try.
They fucking worked.
The entire defense industry was scrambling over this deal.
And the key to it was sitting in 23 shipping containers
in the back of a rusted out warehouse on the other side of the world.
We got back with just enough time
to submit our bid before the government's deadline.
And then we waited.
We waited five months.
Pa.
David!
- Is that Efraim?  - What?
- Is it?  - David!
We fucking won!
Holy shit. We won the Afghan deal.
- What?  - We won the Afghan deal!
- We won?  - We fucking won!
Bro! Are you fucking kidding me?
- We fucking won!  - Yeah, motherfucker!
Yeah! Yeah, motherfucker!
Before we could begin,
AEY still needed to be vetted by the government.
It's a pain-in-the ass process
involving three separate audits
and an in-person interview.
The audits were the biggest hurdle.
I mean, we didn't even have a real bookkeeper.
We didn't have real books.
We had to fabricate AEY's accounting
going back three years.
Ledgers, bank statements, phony purchase orders,
we forged it all.
Two weeks later, we were in Rock Island,
Illinois for our big meeting
with procurement officers from the U.S. Military.
We were pretty fucking nervous.
So Efraim thought it'd be a good idea to get high in the parking lot.
Hold up.
Does it sound like we're more than two people right now?
Yeah.
It was really strong shit.
Okay.
This is very impressive.
Very impressive.
Frankly, we were a tad concerned with your performance history
against a deal of this size.
But after meeting you two face to face,
we feel like we're in good hands on this one.
Well, we won't let you down,
sirs.
Not to mention,
your bid was far too attractive for us to pass up.
Thank you. I mean, that's great to hear because we really worked hard on this.
Sorry. Excuse me.
One of you just said
our bid was too attractive to pass up.
What did you mean by that, exactly?
He means you boys lowballed the shit out of your competition.
Yeah. Uh...
By how much?
Millions.
Okay.
Just for me. I...
I'm curious, how many millions?
Well, technically, we're not supposed to discuss that with you,
but what the hell.
You guys came in $53 million lower than the nearest competition.
Fuck! Fuck!
Motherfucker!
$53 million.
We're okay.
Look at the bright side.
For once, the American taxpayer
is getting a good deal on a defense contract.
Man, fuck the American taxpayer.
Hello?
Iz?
Hey, Ella. Hi.
How are you, sweetie?
Hey. Do you know where her blue sandals are?
Oh, hey.
Um, I'm not sure.
But listen, can we talk for a sec?
Mmm-hmm.
I need to go back to Albania for a couple weeks.
A month, tops.
Sure. No problem.
Hey, what's going on?
Ella and I are going to stay with my mom for a while.
What? What are you talking about?
Iz, what happened?
How come you didn't tell me you went to Iraq?
I was looking for the plumber's number
on your computer and I saw the photos.
I can explain.
You said you never left the hotel room in Jordan.
I know. Because I didn't want to freak you out.
Why is it every time I catch you in a lie
you try to convince me that you lied for my benefit?
At what point do you just admit you're a liar?
Iz, would you stop, please?
We said we'd tell each other everything.
- You promised!  - I know! Okay, I fucked up.
What else aren't you telling me?
- Nothing.  - No.
Seriously.
You know everything now.
Okay. Aren't you going to ask me why I called the plumber?
Yeah, sure. What happened?
The pipe is leaking in the guest bathroom.
I found this.
Let me guess. You didn't want to freak me out?
Okay, hold on.
So I hid some money under the sink.
What's the big deal?
The big deal is you hid it from me!
No, I didn't!
Then who did you hide it from?
I don't know. It was stupid. You're right.
We're going to leave before you think of something else to say.
Iz, I'm sorry.
Iz!
Oh, fuck.
Hey, what's up, man?
What's up?
Just getting ready to leave.
What is that?
I just wanted to thank you for agreeing to go on this trip.
It's not lost on me,
the sacrifice you're making for this company.
And I really appreciate it.
"To my partner, David. The world is yours."
- It's from Scarface.  - Of course, man. I remember.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Uh, hey, before I go,
I just wanted...
What's this?
It's our partnership agreement. 70-30.
I just wanted to make it official.
Yeah, of course.
- It's a good idea.  - Cool.
Man, eight fucking weeks in Albania.
Iz is going to hate me forever.
No, she's going to suck your cock every day for a year.
Because we're on the verge of making $30 million.
Yeah, man.
Go crush it.
Thanks, bro.
Nice.
Hey, you've reached Iz. You know what to do.
Come on, Iz. Don't cut me off like this.
I'm in Albania, at the hotel.
Left the number with your mom.
And if you could please just call me back
because I really miss you. Okay?
And I love you.
Bye.
Good morning, buddy.
Hey, Bashkim.
Oh, I bring you Kolonat. It's our McDonald's.
Yeah, I'm good. But thanks.
We go to work now?
Uh-huh. No, no, no. I said I need two trucks.
Yeah, you just got the one here right now.
Yeah. Look, I got a cargo plane sitting at the airport.
Yeah, I know. I know.
Hey, let me call you right back.
Hey, stop! Stop, stop!
Hold up, hold up, hold up! Hey, turn that off!
What the fuck is that?
Where did you get this?
Yo! What's up?
Hey, man, we got a problem.
- Where you at?  - I'm at Liv, bro.
Trying to bang some Cuban chick who's waiting for me at my table.
Why, what do we got?
Let me get this straight. I'm in Albania right now freezing my ass off.
You're at Liv, trying to get laid?
David, it's 1:00 a.m. here.
I'm blowing off some steam.
Yeah, 1:00 a.m. is when you're supposed to be at the office
because that's the middle of fucking day in every country we do business with.
Look, we got a problem with the AK ammunition.
- What kind of problem?  - It's Chinese.
Chinese, bro? What does that even mean, Chinese?
It means it's from China.
What are you talking about? I was there, I saw the ammo.
We both did.
Yeah, look, I don't know what to tell you.
They fucked us. Okay? We got played.
Hold on. How do you even know it's Chinese?
There's Chinese writing on every fucking crate.
Trust me, it's Chinese.
Yeah.
Henry, what the fuck!
We've been trying to reach you for two days!
It's Efraim and David.
We have a serious fucking problem.
I'm listening.
The AK ammunition, it's Chinese.
What, you think the Afghans who are getting
shot up by the Taliban give a shit where their ammo comes from?
No, but the Pentagon does.
Henry, you know we can't use Chinese!
America has an embargo against China.
You had your boys show us the one crate of Albanian ammo in the entire country.
I'm sorry, did anyone prevent you from inspecting the other crates?
Did you even bother to ask what the country of origin was?
Who the fuck would ask that?
Henry, I'm staring at 100 million rounds
of illegal Chinese ammunition that you sold us.
What are we supposed to do?
Do your fucking job!
The U.S. government wants to look the other way.
Don't give them a reason not to.
And while you're at it, learn the difference between
"We have a problem" and "You have a problem."
Fuck!
We were fucked. The ammo was worthless
and I was stuck in Albania trying to piece together new suppliers
from all over Eastern Europe.
Holy shit.
What the fuck are you doing here, man?
I have a big idea.
How did you get in my room?
They let me in.
I'm a trustworthy guy.
Not only did they let me in, they brought me room service.
Anyway, I have a big fucking idea.
Yeah? What's that?
What if we repack?
Repack what?
The bullets!
What if we repack them all?
100 million rounds?
David, it can be done.
Think about it. We'll also save a fortune on shipping.
We trade out all the big, heavy wooden crates
for light cardboard boxes.
Yeah, but it would still be Chinese ammo.
Look at this towel. Okay?
Turkish. Made in Turkey.
Not anymore. Now it's an Albanian towel.
It's only Chinese if the packaging says it's Chinese.
Yeah. But I mean, that's also fucking illegal, man.
We have two options.
We either repack this shit and send it off
or we can walk away from a $300 million-deal.
What do you want to do?
When you put it like that there's really only one option.
Our driver Bashkim introduced us to his friend
who owned a boxing and storage company out of Tirana.
This is Enver. I grew up with him.
Nice to meet you, Enver.
You too. Bashkim told me a little about your situation.
Yeah, look, to put it simply, we have a weight problem.
We're shipping a large quantity of ammunition
from Albania to Afghanistan.
Right now, it's packed in heavy tins
inside big wooden crates.
And what we would like to do
is to transfer those bullets into plastic bags
and then put those in double-walled,
corrugated fiberboard boxes.
Do you know what those are?
Yeah, of course. For what reason?
We just told you.
What the fuck is it with this country?
The original packaging, it's too heavy.
Too many crates. We need to streamline.
Okay. How many crates?
A lot. It's 100 million rounds of ammunition.
Understood. But how many actual crates?
We have 68,520 crates.
I've seen it.
It's fucking crazy.
Done.
So 50 men, eight weeks.
I can do it for $100,000.
100,000 U.S. dollars?
Yeah.
- Give us a second.  - Yeah. One second, please.
Okay. I'm going to talk very seriously.
It was hard not to laugh.
I mean, not only was this guy saving the entire deal,
but by repacking all the ammo
we would increase our profit margin by almost $3 million.
Where should we get dinner tonight?
There's this place by the hotel. It's pretty good.
Okay. All right, go ahead.
Okay, deal.
It was even better than we thought.
We were trading heavy wooden crates for light cardboard boxes.
Eight ounce tins for plastic bags.
By repacking the ammo,
we would lighten our overall load by 180 tons.
180 fucking tons!
That meant fewer flights using lighter planes burning less fuel.
Which all added up to more money for us.
On December 8th, 2007,
AEY delivered the first 5 million rounds
to the Afghan army.
It went off without a hitch.
Come on, just say it once, sweetie. Come on.
Say "dada." Say "dada."
We really have to go, David.
No, hey, five more minutes, please? Please?
We're about to eat. My mom's waiting.
Ella, wave goodbye to Daddy. Hmm.
Bye-bye, Ella.
Merry Christmas. I love you.
Hey, can you give her to your mom so that we can talk for a minute?
I'm sorry, David.
We'll call you in a couple days. Okay?
Bye.
Hey, this is David.
Bro, you want to hear something totally fucked up?
Merry Christmas, Efraim.
It's Christmas?
That's why nobody's here.
I was about to fire the entire office.
Anyway, when I was over there,
I was talking to our boy, Bashkim.
Did you know his uncle
works at the Albanian defense ministry?
No, I didn't know that.
Well, he does.
So I said, "You know what would be interesting to me, Bashkim?
"I'd be curious to know what Henry is paying the Albanians for the AK ammo."
Efraim?
Do you know what he found out?
That motherfucker is paying two and a half cents a round.
He's charging us a 400% markup!
Yeah. So what? We do the same thing.
Yeah, but this is our contract.
And we almost lost it because of him and his Chinese fucking bullets.
But we didn't lose it.
That's not the point!
I want to figure out a way to cut this cocksucker out of the deal.
Efraim, stop.
No, listen to me.
I'm serious, man.
We're making money, okay?
He's making money, the whole thing is fucking working.
Don't mess with it.
I don't give a fuck. He's ripping us off!
Look, I'm serious, okay?
I'm going to be on the next flight out of here if you pull that shit.
Whoa. Bro, you don't have to threaten me.
All right? I'm your partner.
Yeah, it doesn't always feel like that.
I found this deal. And I'm over here
doing all the work and you're in Miami trying to sabotage it.
How am I sabotaging it?
By trying to fuck over Henry, the way you fuck over everybody else.
You're right. Henry's our partner.
He's the reason we got this deal.
I was just looking out for us and I took it too far.
Don't sweat it, bro. I'll leave it alone.
Thank you.
We can't push our luck with this shit, man.
All right, I'll talk to you soon. Bye.
Whoa. What the fuck? Hey.
Fuck! Stop.
Stop! I don't understand!
Do you understand now?
Yeah. Yes.
Did you really think you could cut me out of my own deal?
Please.
Fuck.
David, we need to talk.
Now's not a good time.
I have not been paid yet.
What do you mean? Like for the month?
Ever.
You haven't been paid anything?
Your partner doesn't return phone calls.
My guys need to be paid.
They are going to stop work.
David, I know the real reason
that you want ammunition repacked.
Okay, look, Enver. Listen to me.
I gotta fly to Miami right now. I'll be back in a week.
But I promise you, the first thing that I'm going do when I land
is make sure you get your money wired, okay?
Okay.
David.
Airport, let's go.
Look, I'm late for a flight. I'll be back next week.
She said her husband didn't come home last night.
Okay, what do you want me to do?
She's very worried. It is not like him.
Tell her I don't know her husband.
Who's your husband?
Bashkim.
No one ever heard from Bashkim again.
They never found a note, they never found a body.
He just fell off the planet.
I was done with Albania.
I was never going back.
Hi.
Hey.
The reason I went to Albania was to repackage Chinese ammunition
so we could disguise it and sell it to the U.S. government.
That sounds illegal.
It is. But I'm done.
I swear, no matter what happens for the rest of my life
I'm never going to lie to you again.
Mmm-hmm.
I love you so much, Iz.
What happened to your nose?
I was kidnapped by Albanian gangsters.
- I think it's broken.  - Oh, my God.
I think I'm going to go back to being a massage therapist.
Is that okay?
Yes.
It was always okay.
Hey, you're back.
Whoa!
Bro, what are you doing back? What happened to your face?
That's everything that's been delivered on the Afghan deal.
I want my cut. I'm out.
What are you talking about?
He put a fucking gun to my head, man.
Who, Henry?
You said that you were going to leave it alone.
Oh, fuck.
I fucked up.
I'm done, Efraim.
Look, you don't have to go back.
I hired this new guy, Ivan.
- He speaks Albanian.  - I'm done.
What, do you think I just got 4 million bucks laying around?
I've thought it through.
I'll take 40 cents on the dollar.
Yeah, I thought it through too.
How about this?
How about zero cents on the dollar?
Let me remind you that we have a contract.
Fuck your contract!
If I asked you to build me a house,
and you quit after building me half a house, you think I owe you half the money?
Is this a fucking joke, David?
You have two weeks. Otherwise, you'll hear from my lawyer.
Who, Warren?
Are you talking about Warren? He's my lawyer too.
I introduced you to him.
Fucking Warren.
Fuck!
AEY. How may I direct your call?
We fight.
Fight with our families,
fight with our business associates.
Sometimes we fight with our friends.
If God were here,
we'd probably fight with Him too.
Efraim has a heavy heart over what's happened.
No offense, Ralph, but I'm not sure you've ever met the real Efraim.
He's a complicated young man.
But he just wants to sit down and talk.
Find a fair solution.
He's asked me to mediate.
Let me help you, David.
I just don't know if I'm ready yet.
All right, here he is.
Hey, bro.
Good to see you.
Sorry things have gotten so crazy.
Yeah. Me too.
You having anything, hon?
I'll just have a coffee. Thanks.
I've thought about it a lot.
And I don't want you to walk away from this empty-handed.
Cool.
So I had Warren draft up a severance agreement.
And I think it's pretty fair.
I'm prepared to pay you 50K per year for the next four years.
200 grand?
Is this a fucking joke, man?
Is this what you meant by mediation?
In all fairness, there was never
a partnership agreement, no prior contract.
Yeah. I have something better than a partnership agreement.
I have proof.
Before I left Albania, I took everything.
What the fuck.
All the documents we forged, photos of repacking.
- David!  - Repacking?
- He didn't tell you?  - David!
Oh, yeah, we took that money you gave us,
and we bought 100 million rounds of illegal Chinese ammunition,
then we repackaged it and sold it to the U.S. Military.
Yeah, and we made $8 million doing it, asshole.
Careful, Efraim.
We told Ralph we only made $3 million on that one.
Wait, what now?
He sends you fake accounting reports every month.
- Oh, fuck off.  - I make them on my laptop.
Now you're just making shit up.
Really? Because I kept everything, you dumb fuck!
I even have copies of the bank statements that we photoshopped
and sent to the government.
Get the fuck out of here.
I can bury you.
Us.
I think you meant to say,
you can bury us.
Because anything that implicates me,
implicates you as well.
- Efraim, wait.  - No, no, no.
I came here today prepared to pay you $200,000.
Now I'm not even going to pay for breakfast.
Oh. What's going on over here? Huh?
Hello?
May I speak with David Packouz?
- Yeah, who's this?  - Hi, David.
This is C. J. Chivers with The New York Times.
I was wondering if you had a minute to talk about AEY,
and the alleged repackaging of Chinese ammunition.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Well, according to my source, there's an ongoing investigation
at the State Department.
And I was hoping to get some clarification...
David, this sounds pretty serious.
Yeah, I know.
Maybe you should call my uncle.
The lawyer.
Oh, my God. Okay.
That's a good idea.
Hey, give me a minute. I'll meet you guys in the lobby.
You just get a call from The New York Times?
Yeah.
Me too.
You know, Scarface was on TV last night,
and I was watching it and thinking about when we were little
and we used to do the lines from the movie.
You're my best friend, David.
God, I really fucked this up, didn't I?
I'm sorry, bro.
Wow.
Are you ever not acting, man?
What does that mean?
You just tell me what you think I want to hear,
because The New York Times called,
and you're freaking out that I might say something.
Just admit it.
We were never best friends.
You were just playing the part of my best friend.
Yeah.
Scarface wasn't even on TV last night.
You're such a piece of shit.
- Fuck!  - Fuck you.
- Fuck.  - Little bitch.
Well, that saves us a trip.
Out of all the illegal shit we did,
all the lies we told the government,
in the end, the thing that did us in?
Yes, I'm trying to reach the Department of Defense, please.
Efraim never paid the box guy.
To who do you report a crime?
After Enver called the Pentagon,
the State Department launched a full-scale investigation,
that went on for months.
They busted Ralph at one of his shops in the middle of a work day.
He was horrified and couldn't make a deal fast enough.
All that bullshit about him wanting to mediate a truce between Efraim and I...
It was a setup.
Oh, yeah, we took that money you gave us,
and we bought 100 million rounds of illegal Chinese ammunition,
then we repackaged it and sold it to the U.S. Military.
They had us dead to rights.
It was pathetic.
While going through Efraim's computer, they even found a to-do list that said,
"Repackage Chinese ammo. "
The story tonight that has Pentagon officials scrambling.
How did two 20-something young men land a big Pentagon contract?
Federal agents arrested both men last week, charging them with fraud
for selling outdated, defective Chinese ammunition
to the Pentagon.
Efraim was charged with over 70 federal crimes
and sentenced to four years in prison.
I pled guilty and was sentenced to seven months house arrest.
Congress called the Afghanistan contract a case study
in all that is wrong with the government's procurement process.
In 2022, AEY will be eligible once again to bid on Federal contracts.
How's it going?
It's okay.
If I wanted you dead, you'd already be dead.
I guess it's going all right then.
Come in.
How's your baby?
It's a girl, right?
Yeah. She's good.
I got three.
All girls.
They tell you it gets better.
That's not true, it gets worse.
That's why I like the arms business.
No women.
I want to apologize about Albania.
I had bad information.
So you stuffed me in the trunk of a car and shoved a gun in my face by mistake?
Yeah.
I'm not a bad man, but in certain situations,
I have to ask myself,
what would a bad man do?
I appreciate you leaving my name out of your testimony.
I didn't really see a reason to include it.
Yeah, but still.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
When we met in Vegas at the blackjack table,
was that a coincidence?
What do you think?
Can I ask you another question?
My driver in Albania went missing.
Do you know what happened to him?
It's a piece of my end on the Afghan deal.
It's for you.
No more questions.